<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 12:29:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-08: I&#39;m stoked about surfing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 12:29:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-08/</guid>
      <description>Today, I surfed in this morning and this evening. The waves size are from shoulder to head, it&amp;rsquo;s high for me. It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to getting out to out-side.
I rode waves only a few times, and wiped out many times. The sea is fairly cold that I might caught a bit cold. Still, I enjoyed surfing very much and I will keep surfing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-07: Master of Life</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-07/</guid>
      <description>My goal through my life is to be a &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo;. The word, &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo;, was told in the comic &amp;ldquo;Master Keaton&amp;rdquo;.
&amp;ldquo;Master of life&amp;rdquo; is a person who lives life in his own way and always has the life of his own colour. &amp;ldquo;Master Keaton vol.7&amp;rdquo; Chapter 3, page.79
It&amp;rsquo;s my goal, but I have not reached there at all. But I believe I will be able to become &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo; someday, if I can continue studying for a lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-06: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</guid>
      <description>I use a textbook &amp;ldquo;TOUCHSTONE 2nd edition Student&amp;rsquo;s Book Level 3&amp;rdquo; in my English lesson. It&amp;rsquo;s at the low intermediate CFER level (A2-B1).
The followings are the homework I have to do by tomorrow.
page.5: Lesson-B 3.C Who do you admire ? I admire my brother.
Why ? Because, he works as a engineer in America. I also want to work as a engineer in America or Europe. I envy him working abroad and I&amp;rsquo;m proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-05: The English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</guid>
      <description>I took an English conversation lesson, it&amp;rsquo;s the first time I came back from my honeymoon.
I have visited England, Scotland, Canada and America in my honeymoon, so I thought that my English skill improve a little bit maybe, but it&amp;rsquo;s not at all.
I will study English harder than before so I can work abroad. Of course, I want to enjoy studying English. The proverb says, &amp;ldquo;what one likes, one will do well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-02: Start Learning python</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 19:32:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-02/</guid>
      <description>I bought this class a year ago, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t been studying python so much recently. I&amp;rsquo;ll try learning python again for improving my programming skill.
This class is very good and reasonable price. I think it fits people who want to study python for the first time. Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s fun for me to study python. I&amp;rsquo;ll learn python in a fun way from now on.
The progress of studying python is managed by the following github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-01: Jogging</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:14:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-01/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to surf if the waves were high, but today the waves were too small to surf.
I have jogged along Shonan Coast for the first time in two weeks this evening.
The weather was a bit cloudy, but it was very nice.
I think I have to do exercise, because I have been gaining weight from before, I will continue to jog from now on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-31: AWS DeepRacer League Workshop</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:10:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</guid>
      <description>AWS DeepRace League - Technical Workdshop Yesterday, I joined the &amp;ldquo;AWS Deep Racer League - Technical Workhop&amp;rdquo;, because I wanted to have fun learning about machine learning. The AWS DeepRacer is a 1&amp;frasl;18 scale racing car and it makes it possible to learn Reinforcement Learning (RL) in a fun way. It was disappointing that the hands-on was disabled due to a failure of the AWS service.
The presenter explained DeepRacer&amp;rsquo;s Reinforcement Learning and its simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-30: Surfed for the first time in two years</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 08:17:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I surfed for the first time in two years. The waves were waist high and very good for me. The water temperature was still a little cold and I needed a wetsuit.
Surfing after a long time was very pleasant and fun, I felt like going to keep surfing from now on.
This is the surfboard I used. It&amp;rsquo;s the Softech&amp;rsquo;s soft-surfboard: SALLY FITZGIBBONS SIGNATURE 7&amp;rsquo;0&amp;rdquo;. This long, buoyant surfboard is good for me because I am not strong and underexercised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-29: A TED talk that impressed me</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 07:48:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to build your confidence - and spark it others&amp;rdquo; I lose my confidence when I fail and disappointed myself,
when I was given cold stares, when I was blamed, and
when I was ignored.
This TED talk, Ms. Brittany Packnett&amp;rsquo;s speech, gives me a confidence.
It tells me that I need not lose my confidence.
Impressed words  Confidence is the necessary spark before everything that follows. Permission births confidence, community nurtures it and curiosity affirms it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1 in London</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</guid>
      <description>Immigration I got a little bit nervous at immigration, because I usually get asked many questions at the immigration examination and I can&amp;rsquo;t answer well.
This time, however, immigration officers are very kind. Moreover, my wife said &amp;ldquo;This is our honeymoon&amp;rdquo; then, they said to us &amp;ldquo;Conguraturations!&amp;rdquo; with smile.
Tube We went to the center of London city by Tube: it&amp;rsquo;s subway in London. To ride Tube, we bought Oyster card at the station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</guid>
      <description>The day before depature We decided to carry out our luggage by Sagawa Express to the Handea airport. The luggage was to be carried by the carrier the day before. Until the day I was very busy with packing.
That day I could not sleep much because of excitement.
The depature day, at the airport The plane we were to ride was at 11:35. We wanted to arrive at the airport two hours ago, so we left home at 7:30.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>