<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-18: it&#39;s rainy today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</guid>
      <description>In yesterday English lesson, I had my teacher check my blog again and reviewed Unit-4, and then finished it. And I started to learn Unit-5 and found that my teacher eats crisps too much.
I learned the following vocabularies.
 philanthropist  I told my teacher about my uncle who is keen on volunteering and then my teacher called him a philanthropist.  divorce and annulment  I didn&amp;rsquo;t know the word annulment, and so I can&amp;rsquo;t understand the difference between divorce and annulment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-17: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-17/</guid>
      <description>The pleasure of summer vacation My family used to go to Nagashima Resort in the summer, when I was a kid. Back then, I was always looking forward to going Nagashima Resort every summer. Both now and then, Nagashima Resort is the biggest amusement park in Kansai region; it has a tremendous pool, various water slides and roller coasters.
Nowadays, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to an Amusement park. I don&amp;rsquo;t like going crowded places these days because I get tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-16: Last weekend</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-16/</guid>
      <description>Today, I worked at the office. This week, the progress of my work isn&amp;rsquo;t so good, because what I tried to end this week didn&amp;rsquo;t end. The reason is the lack of understanding machine learning.
I wanted to start training my machine learning model this week. I cannot start it tomorrow probably. Definitely. It can&amp;rsquo;t be helped. Next week I&amp;rsquo;ll try.
Last weekend typhoon no.19 came, however, I had no damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-11: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-11-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-11-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson D: Family activities 1. Reading A. Yes, we did. I and my family used to eat together every dinner. We used to talk about what we did and how we feel. Plus, we used to talk about neighbours, friends, relatives, and TV show, movies, everything.
B: Why does Barbara think families should eat together more often? Because children who have regular meals with their families feel less stressed, have a healthier weight, get better grades, and are less likely to get into trouble than children from families that don&amp;rsquo;t eat together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-10: How to summarize an article</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:24:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Points  Rephrase the words and expressions used in the article to your own words and expressions Don&amp;rsquo;t mistake the conclusion Don&amp;rsquo;t claim your own idea  the author points out &amp;hellip; the author feels &amp;hellip;  Ignore examples sentences and modifiers  Procedure  Read whole the article at first  Distinguish between story trunks and branches  Write out the most important claims  They should be at the beginning and end  Write out an important statement of each paragraphs Rephrase them to your own words and expressions  Use &amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo; when quoting a sentence   Summary of Barbara&amp;rsquo;s Blog  Overview  About taking meals with the family The author feels that families have little time together at mealtimes these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-07: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-07-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-07-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson C: If you ask me, &amp;hellip; 3. Strategies: In my opinion A. 1. I don&amp;rsquo;t agree with that. You should get married when you want to.
2. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if you&amp;rsquo;d better to have lots of friends. You should do what you want.
3. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s right.
4. I partly agree with it.
B. divorce and children I suppose that divorce can be terrible for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-04: New teacher</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:13:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-04/</guid>
      <description>A new teacher will be in charge of my English class from today. I will have to introduce myself to the new teacher. What should I talk about?
1. Greeting Good evening.
2. Your name I&amp;rsquo;m Naoki Morita.
3. Location I was born and raised in Mie prefecture, but now live in Fujisawa-city. I&amp;rsquo;ve been living in Fuisawa-city for three years.
4. Position and Company I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-04: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-04-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-04-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson C: If you ask me, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: Agreeing 1.  It&amp;rsquo;s really bad for kids, when they come home from school to an empty house. Remember when one parent used to stay at home with the kids? Nowadays, both parents are at work. 
That&amp;rsquo;s true. But a lot of families need two incomes these days.
2.  A lot of families don&amp;rsquo;t have meals together anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-27: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-27-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-27-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson C: If you ask me, &amp;hellip; 1.D Complete these sentences with expressions from above to give your opinions.
1. I don&amp;rsquo;t agree that people work longer hours than they used to. Until thirty years ago in Japan, I think that all Japanese used to work really harder than now. My father also used to work harder everyday, even Saturday, sometimes also Sunday. At that age, however, there were hope like that we can get more money, get own car and house, and become happier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-25: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-25-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-25-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson B: Family memories 2. Grammar: used to and would  My family used to go to the beach in the summer. We&amp;rsquo;d go almost every weekend. My mother used to make a lunchbox for us when I was in a junior high school and high school. She&amp;rsquo;d make it every weekday. My brother and I used to play football together, when I was in an elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-20: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-20-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-20-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson B: Family memories 2. Grammar: used to and would  My family used to go to the beach in the summer. We&amp;rsquo;d go almost every weekend. My mother used to make a lunchbox for us when I was in a junior high school and high school. She&amp;rsquo;d make it every weekday. My brother and I used to play football together, when I was in an elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-18: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-18-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-18-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson A: Family gripes 3. Listening and speaking: Reasonable demands? B. 1. My parents have their own company. You know, they sell all different kinds of bottle of water. And they want me to get in the board of that and be part of it. Like, my Mom wants me to learn more about bottle of water and everything. I&amp;rsquo;m not really into it. But, Mom said sure teach me all about it when I finish college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-13: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-13-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-13-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4: Family life Lesson A: Family gripes Kids gripe about their parents&amp;hellip; Every day, my mother urges me to &amp;ldquo;Take a bath now.&amp;rdquo;, when I&amp;rsquo;m watching TV.
Parents gripe about their kids&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;
Spouses gripe about each other&amp;hellip; My wife sometimes interrupts me and tells her story. If I interrupted her or didn&amp;rsquo;t listen to her, I would certainly be scolded.
1. Getting started A. My wife sometimes allocates me some chores: cleaning the bathrooms, the toilet, the Roomba or tidying up cardboard, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-11: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-11-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-11-homework/</guid>
      <description>Checkpoint Units 1-3 5. What do you think?  What&amp;rsquo;s the tallest building in this city?  Yokohama Landmark Tower is the tallest.  What&amp;rsquo;s the nicest park around here?  I have no idea about the nicest, because I&amp;rsquo;ve never been to a park around here.  Where&amp;rsquo;s the best place to sit and enjoy the view?  The restaurant in Yokohama Landmark Tower is the best. Because it has a magnificent night view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-10: WFM</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-10/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home last Friday and yesterday, and I work at the office today, so I came to the office for the first time in 4 days today.
The reason why I came to the office is to access the server with GPU in my company. I want to use it to learn Deep Learning. There is no other reason.
Thus, if I don&amp;rsquo;t use it, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to go to the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-09: WFM due to a typhoon</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 20:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-09/</guid>
      <description>Typhoon Faxai (Typhoon No.15) came in this morning. It was heavy rain and the wind was blowing hard. All train was stopped until 8 o&amp;rsquo;clock, so I decided to work from home today. In the Kanto region, there were restrictions on the number of visitors to the stations, and it seemed very crowded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-04: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-04-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-04-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson D: Is that a fact? 2. Speaking and writing: Interesting facts  What is the highest mountain?  Mount Fuji is the highest. It&amp;rsquo;s 3,776 meters high.  What is the longest river?  The Shinano River is the longest. It&amp;rsquo;s 367 kilo meters.  What is the longest bridge?  The Aqua Bridge is the longest. It&amp;rsquo;s 4,424 meters long.  What is the tallest building?  The Tokyo Skytree is the tallest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-01: Running along the Kugenuma beach</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of summer vacation. It was very hot and humid again today. I went to JA to by vegetables and went to a supermarket to buy some foods and drinks in the morning.
I ate Shiroishi-Umen for lunch. I ate it for the first time and it was delicious. The noodles are short and easy to eat, and my wife made the soup for me. It&amp;rsquo;s so tasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-30: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-30-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-30-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson C: I had the best time. 3. Listening and strategies: Travel talk 1. What&amp;rsquo;s the most interesting place you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to? Isle of Skye and Highlands. It&amp;rsquo;s a medieval English scene I saw in a movie.
2. What&amp;rsquo;s the most beautiful place you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen? Niagara Falls. It&amp;rsquo;s most powerful and beautiful falls.
3. What&amp;rsquo;s the best trip you&amp;rsquo;ve taken? Honeymoon. British fish&amp;amp;chips and ale are the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-28: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-28-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-28-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson C: I had the best time. 3. Listening and strategies: Travel talk Ray Welcome to Travel talk. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Ray Martin. My guest today is travel writer, Jill Ryan. Jill has traveled around the world many times. Her new book is called &amp;ldquo;A travelers&amp;rsquo; tales&amp;rdquo;. Jill, welcome to Travel talk.
Jill Thank you, Ray. It&amp;rsquo;s great to be here.
Ray Jill, you have the most interesting life. You clearly love traveling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-25: Dragon Quest Builders 2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-25/</guid>
      <description>I bought the nintendo switch&amp;rsquo;s game, &amp;ldquo;Dragon Quest Builders 2&amp;rdquo;, before. I played with it today after a long time. I started it from noon and it was night when I realized.
I wasted my life&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-24: heat stroke or cold</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Today, I bought some vegetables at a grocery store of JA, and I went to a clinic near my home to get a cold medicine.
I&amp;rsquo;m not feeling well recently. I have a runny nose and lots of sneeze, and I&amp;rsquo;m dull. I think it&amp;rsquo;s probably because of air conditioning during sleep.
However, I can&amp;rsquo;t stop the air conditioner while sleeping. If I do that, I will get heat stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-23: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-23-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-23-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson C: I had the best time. 1. Conversation Strategy: Being supportive listener A. Q. Are there any national parks in your country? Yes, there are. Japan has about 30 national parks.
Q. Which one is the most beautiful? Yakushima is the most beautiful one, I think. Yakushima became the first World heritage site in Japan.
Q. Which one is the largest? Daisetsuzan National Park is the largest one. It&amp;rsquo;s 2,267 square kilometers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-22: A one-day business trip to Osaka</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Today, I went to Osaka to get a lecture of AI.
I always buy the following this.
It&amp;rsquo;s the most famous steamed bun with meat filling in Japan, especially in Kansai region. I stayed in the line for about twenty minutes to buy it.
And then, I ate the following this because I had enough time before the departure of the Shinkansen.
It&amp;rsquo;s also famous ramen in Kansai region. The last time I ate it was when I was a graduate student, about 15 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-20: a report</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 18:40:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-20/</guid>
      <description>Today I finally submitted a report of AI training. I was tired of studying AI this summer vacation. But what I was studying was machine learning, and what I really had to learn was deep learning. I wil continue to study AI.
I want to learn deep learning quickly and develop various application softwares using deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-20: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-20-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-20-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson A: Human wonders (page.23) 2. Grammar A. 1. What&amp;rsquo;s the largest city? Tokyo is the largest city in Japan.
2. Which airport has the most flights every day? Haneda airport has the most flights in Japan.
3. What&amp;rsquo;s the fastest way to travel. Shinkansen or a aircraft is the fastest way to travel in Japan.
4. What&amp;rsquo;s the most beautiful region? Around Mt.Fuji is the most beautiful region in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-14: Japanese cuisine in yukata</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-14/</guid>
      <description>I and my wife went to Kurumaya in Fujisawa. Kurumaya had a special service for summer only. Yukata and japanese cuisine were included in the set, and the Kimono teacher dressed us in yukata. In addition, a professional photographer took a picture of us.
The meal was very delicious. We will definitely be there next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-09: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-09-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-09-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit.3: Wonders of the world Before you begin &amp;hellip; Have you ever done any of these things? Which would you really like to do?
See an active volcano. Yes, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen an active volcano, Mt.Sakura-jima. It&amp;rsquo;s a most famous active volcano in Japan. It often spews smoke and ashes, but not molten rocks.
Go hiking in a beautiful canyon. Yes, I&amp;rsquo;ve hiked in a beautiful canyon, Takachiho. Takachiho is famous as the place where the grandson of the sun goddess descended from heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-07: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-07-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-07-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson D: Travel blogs (page.19) 2. Listening A. So, yeah. I guess Suzanne has having a really fun trip in New Zealand. Have you read her blog?
No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know she was writing one. So what&amp;rsquo;s she doing?
Well, yesterday, she went hang-gliding. She said she was really scared.
Was she? I&amp;rsquo;m not surprised. You know Suzanne. She&amp;rsquo;s always been scared of trying anything new.
Yeah. Fortunately, she was with a friend, she says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-05: The surgery&#39;s done</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-05/</guid>
      <description>The surgery began at 9:00 am. The surgery was scheduled to end in 6 to 8 hours, but it took 11 hours. The doctor who mainly operated the surgery told us that the bleeding didn&amp;rsquo;t stop for a while and he hesitated to continue operating. Fortunately, the bleeding stopped and he continued. That is the reason that it took long time.
Moreover, he said that this cancer might have metastasized to the liver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-04: Miyazaki</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-04/</guid>
      <description>I and my wife came to Miyazaki city to visit my father-in-law who is going to have an surgery tomorrow.
He has been at a hospital in Miyazaki city from 31 July and had some health checks for the surgery. He looked fine, but he was a little bit nervous. Because he&amp;rsquo;s never stayed at a hospital and had a surgery. He seemed to be bearing up so as not to worry his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-03: Clean my laptop XPS 13</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-03/</guid>
      <description>I cleaned my laptop XPS 13.
I have used my laptop as Xubuntu 18.04 LTS, but unfortunately, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t activate the function of palm-detection. So I had to use a mouse and it was very tiring.
I re-installed Ubuntu-18.04.2 LTS into my laptop XPS 13. Fortunately, palm-detection works! I can&amp;rsquo;t understand why it works, but I&amp;rsquo;m released from a mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-02: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-02-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 17:25:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-02-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson D: Travel blogs (page.19) 1. Reading He had a flat tire on the way to Ipala Volcano. Hard rain soaked everything outside the tent.
She missed Carnival in Rio that she&amp;rsquo;s always wanted to see. And she lost her camera.
2. Listening A. So, yeah. I guess Suzanne has having a really fun trip in New Zealand. Have you read her blog?
No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know she was writing one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-01: The ice age</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-01/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hot and humid today.
I worked at office today, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to commute. Because it was too hot to walk a little and I was sweaty. I was about to get heatstroke.
I hate too hot summer. I wish the ice age would come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-31: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 16:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-31/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go out because it&amp;rsquo;s been hot these days. Getting on a crowded train on such a hot day is hell. But, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go Yokohama to take an English conversation lesson now. I&amp;rsquo;ll come back alive somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-31: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-31-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 09:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-31-homework/</guid>
      <description>Lesson C: I&amp;rsquo;ve heard good things &amp;hellip; (page.16) 1. Conversation Strategy: Keeping the conversation going A. What kinds of fun things do people do on the weekend? Make a list.  going shopping watching movie doing exercise  B. What fun things has Jason done lately? He has gone to a new club called Fizz last week.
C. Find other examples in the conversation.  Have you been there ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-30: My lunch</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-30/</guid>
      <description>I forgot to bring my lunch today. My wife blamed me, saying, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s terrible that you didn&amp;rsquo;t take it even though I made it when I was sick&amp;rdquo;. I apologized to her and got her to forgive me somehow.
So today&amp;rsquo;s lunch was a rice ball and a sandwich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-29: WFM</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:21:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-29/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today and last Friday.
Japanese government encouraged office workers to work from home last week and this week. Because the Tokyo Olympics will be held at the same time next year. They want to control the traffic jam at that time.
Therefore, I worked from home last Monday, last Friday and today. Moreover, I&amp;rsquo;ll work from home next Wednesday and next Friday, too.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to work from home everyday, because it&amp;rsquo;s very tiring to commute every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-24: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-24-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-24-homework/</guid>
      <description>2. My favorite summer memory is My favorite summer memory is that I rode overhead waves five years ago.
At that time I lived in Fukuoka, but I used to go to Hyuga,Miyazaki for camping and surfing.
I had been camping in Hyuga that summer, and a typhoon came. The typhoon passed near my campsite in the middle of the night and left to the east. In the early morning of the next day, the wind calmed and the big wave remained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-19: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-19-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 11:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-19-homework/</guid>
      <description>1. This summer I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to This summer I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to learn algebra and statistics.
I learned algebra and statistics when I was in high school and university, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t used them very much recently. Because I used to use sophisticated software libraries, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to use them.
However, I have to use them from now on to understand the theory of machine learning and deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-18: a wonderful meeting</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 23:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-18/</guid>
      <description>I went to Osaka to get a lecture for Deep Learning.
I usually get motion sickness when I work on a PC while riding Shinkansen, but this time I took a preventative medicine for motion sickness, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel anything wrong.
About 20 people have participated in the AI training, and each group of 4 people will work on exercises. The final challenge of this training is to challenge the Amazon Robotics Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-17: homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-17-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-17-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 2. Experiences Lesson B Unusual experiences 1. Building language A. Which experience do you think was scarier ? I think Martin&amp;rsquo;s experience is scarier. I&amp;rsquo;m introverted and bad at singing, so if I were him, I would be scared to sing in front of many people and my legs would shave.
B. Unscramble the questions and complete the answers. Then practice with a partner.  1.A: Have you ever been to Ecuador?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-12: a longer conversation</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-12/</guid>
      <description>How to make a conversation longer. The best way to show that you want to start a longer conversation is to ask open-ended questions. Open-ended questions have to be answered with more than one word and allow the other person to talk longer.
1. Open-ended questions  What do you think about hoge? Have you heard that hoge? (If they answer &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;: ) What do you think? What do you like about hoge?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-11: I don&#39;t know AI yet.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 19:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-11/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying a development environment for AI(ML/DL). I haven&amp;rsquo;t studied AI itself yet. Despite that, there are too many things I don&amp;rsquo;t know and I have a lot to learn.
It feels so good to know what I didn&amp;rsquo;t know. There are many such moments since I started studying AI.
It feels so good to try new things at any age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-10: the beginning of busy days?</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-10/</guid>
      <description>I started to be busy from this week. Because I&amp;rsquo;m assigned to a new task. It&amp;rsquo;s about Deep Learning as known as Artificial Intelligence. It&amp;rsquo;s used for self-driving, advanced driving assistance, driver monitoring, and so on.
I&amp;rsquo;ll take it easy. I think it&amp;rsquo;s the most efficient to work hard at ease. Don&amp;rsquo;t take it too seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-10: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-10-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-10-homework/</guid>
      <description>Free talk (p.129) Unit 1. What are we like? I asked me all the questions.
   Find someone who&amp;hellip; Notes     reads very fast. No, I don&amp;rsquo;t. I read a page over and over again.   gets impatient easily. No, I don&amp;rsquo;t. I think I&amp;rsquo;m patient unless someone is rude to me.   is incredibly organized. No, I&amp;rsquo;m not. My desk is disorganized, so I&amp;rsquo;m not good at organizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-09: A new task</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-09/</guid>
      <description>It held a first meeting of my new task, deep learning for Embedded device. As a first milestone, I&amp;rsquo;m going to build a deep learning development environment on NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Jetson TX2 development kit.
And I&amp;rsquo;m going to participate in Deep Learning training. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting to try new technique. But it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to learn new technique. I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-08: Insomnia?</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-08/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well for some reason last night. I have no idea about the reason. Maybe because of my bed. It&amp;rsquo;s a small to sleep with me and my wife. Because it&amp;rsquo;s a semi-double size bed, it&amp;rsquo;s obvious.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to buy a new queen size bed and a good mattress to sleep well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-07: Tanabata festival</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-07/</guid>
      <description>Today was Tanabata festival. But I caught a cold the day before and I feel sick again today.
I went to a car dealer to repair my car this afternoon. My car was damaged during my vacation the month before last. I rented an Impreza XV as a loaner. It felt a little tight because it&amp;rsquo;s little lower than Forester, my car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-06: I caught a cold</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-06/</guid>
      <description>I caught a cold. I had a runny nose, a headache, and muscle pain. So, I stayed at home all day. I was thinking of going surfing, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t.
It&amp;rsquo;s a pity to catch a cold even though it&amp;rsquo;s a holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-05: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 17:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-05/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. Working from home, I&amp;rsquo;m glad need not to commute. On fridays, stations are crowded and I don&amp;rsquo;t like that.
If I can, I want to work from home everyday.
By the way, my credit card was used illegally. Actually, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay for them. However, I have to reissue my credit card so I cannot use it for a while. In addition, I will need to update the credit card information on my various payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-05: homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-05-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 16:08:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-05-homework/</guid>
      <description>Unit 2. Experiences Lesson A Hopes and dreams 1. Getting Started B. Listen. What is each person&amp;rsquo;s secret dream ? Do you have any secret dreams like these ? Jill Richardson Her secret dream is to study acting.
Sonia and Carlos Silva Their secret dream is to buy their own sailboat.
Raquel Garza Her secret dream is to go surfing.
Hiro Tanaka His secret dream is to take his parents to Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-04: Embedded AI</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-04/</guid>
      <description>Today, my boss make a proposal me about my new job. I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in it. It&amp;rsquo;s about embedded AI. There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of talk about AI in every industry these days. If I do the work, it will improve my technical ability and lead to the next new and interesting work. The person in charge will explain the detail of the proposal to me next week. Whatever the content, I will accept this proposal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-03: Time flies in English lessons</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-03/</guid>
      <description>I had an English lesson today. I feel I&amp;rsquo;ve not improve English skill very much. Maybe I have to study English harder everyday.. I should do my best effort to learn English, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t I ?
The followings is my homework.
Describe 5 celebrities, share their personality and habits.  Kuro-chan, who is a comedian, is incredibly dishonest. He is always lying. Matchan, of the comedy duo &amp;ldquo;Downtown&amp;rdquo;, is extremely funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-02: Is airweave good?</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-02/</guid>
      <description>I had trouble falling asleep last night. Because It was hot and humid night.
I heard that the function of the brain is blunted like drunken if you don&amp;rsquo;t have enough sleep.
That is certainly true. My head was fuzzy and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t concentrate.
In these day, I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of buying a bigger bed that is comfortable to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-01: Running along the Kugenuma coast</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-01/</guid>
      <description>I have been running along the Kugenuma coast. That was the first time in a month. It was very humid and hot, but it was nice to run along the seafront at night.
On the sandy beach, the construction of a sea house was being promoted at night, and I felt the arrival of summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-30: Strong onshore wind and High waves</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-30/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking of surfing today as I did yesterday. So I went to surf. But, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t surf, I was almost drown.
The low pressure made strong onshore winds and high waves, making it difficult for me to surf. They disturbed me trying to go outside.
The wind was weak early in the morning, so I wish I had gone surfing at that time.
In the afternoon, I watched a drama broadcasted on NETFLIX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-29: Going out for drinking in Noge, Yokohama</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-29/</guid>
      <description>Today, I went out for drinking with my wife and friends in Noge, Yokohama. It was drizzling rain, but I&amp;rsquo;m glad it didn&amp;rsquo;t rain heavily.
We went to three Izakaya bars. In Noge, there are many Izakaya bars, so people go to some Izakaya bars to enjoy various dishes and drinks.
One of our friends traveled to Spain for a week in early June. She gave us some presents. We were very happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-28: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 18:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-28/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. I had written documents for my software about its architecture, usage, how to build and installation.
The reason what I worked from home today was that the typhoon was supposed to come. But it went to somewhere. There were no winds, no heavy rain and no lightning.
The weather was so fine and hot today. It&amp;rsquo;s a season that requires air conditioning.
I will go surfing tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-27: It&#39;s a tiresome rainy day.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-27/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s still raining today, however I forgot to bring my umbrella. Oh my gosh&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s, however, just drizzling rain.
The followings will be my homework by tomorrow.
Unit 2. Experiences (page.11) Think of some special experiences you hope to have in the future. Tell the class&amp;hellip;
a place you&amp;rsquo;d like to go someday. I have many places I&amp;rsquo;d like to go. One of those is Iceland.
something you&amp;rsquo;d love to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-26: The usual day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-26/</guid>
      <description>I got an English lesson today. I had a quiz that you make one word by choosing two memos from the ones with one word.
 back pack butter fly light house blue berry etc.  I thought it&amp;rsquo;s easy, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find some words. I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough vocabulary.
The followings will be my homework by next Friday.
page.10: Vocabulary notebook 1. Rewrite the sentences so that they have an opposite meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-25: sunny day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-25/</guid>
      <description>Today is sunny weather during the rainy season. The air temperature is high and humidity is also high, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s better than a rainy day.
Apart from that, Zozomat was announced. It measures your foot shape three-dimensionally in millimeters.
It&amp;rsquo;s a great innovation because I have had several mistakes in selecting shoes. It will be delivered this winter, so I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-24: It&#39;s raining today again</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-24/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s raining today again.
Last night, May beetle was sticking to my cloth that was hanging out.
Summer is coming.
The followings is my homework by next Wednesday.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t hear some of what they said. I should ask my teacher about them.
page.9: Lesson-D 2.Listening Listen to five people talk about themselves. Match the people and the things they will probably say next.
1. Ana I started lessons when I was in elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-23: One punch man</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-23/</guid>
      <description>Today, I spent a depraved day. I watched anime all day long. It was One punch man.
This is an animation in which a hero plays an active role, but what is different from normal animation is that the main hero of this animation is troubled because he is too strong. He is too strong so that he beats any enemy with a single punch. He has lost the purpose of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-22: a relaxing day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-22/</guid>
      <description>Today is a relaxing day.
I woke up at 10:00 o&amp;rsquo;clock on a late morning than usual. And then, I sent the packages which at the post office.
I had Taiwan ramen of a restaurant called Misen which is famouse in Nagoya for lunch. It was very hot and tasted wonderful.
After lunch, I took a nap for 1 hour. I went to surfing. The waves wasn&amp;rsquo;t very high, but at least it was just right for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-21: work from home</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-21/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. Working from home is a lot easier as I don&amp;rsquo;t have to commute. Because it takes 1 hour and half to commute.
And more, there is no toilet problem. In Office, after lunch, almost toilets are always full. Reforming working style should be started from the toilet.
And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have a English lesson this evening. The following is today&amp;rsquo;s homework.
Page.8: Lesson-D 1:Reading A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-19: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-19/</guid>
      <description>The following is homework I have to do by this evening.
Page.7: Lesson-C 3.Strategies -Funny little habits- C. Talk about people with habits like these. Think of something positive to say. texting  My friend is always texting, even during talking. But at least his tweets are interesting.  chewing gum  Some people is always chewing gum, event at a formal event. But at least chewing gum calms their mind down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-18: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-18/</guid>
      <description>The following is homework I have to do by tomorrow.
Page.6: Lesson-C 1.D Change the underlined parts of these sentences to describe habits. Use always and a continuous verb.
 I&amp;rsquo;m pretty disorganized. I lose things.
I&amp;rsquo;m always losing things. Everyone in my family loves music. We sing together.
We&amp;rsquo;re always singing together. My brother is really generous with his time. He fixes my computer.
He&amp;rsquo;s always fixing my computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-16: Eel</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-16/</guid>
      <description>On Father&amp;rsquo;s day, my family ate eel. I love eels very much. Eel is just awesome.
Sadly, however, the number of eels has been decreasing. It&amp;rsquo;s said that the reasons are overfishing and environmental change.
Since the ecology of eels isn&amp;rsquo;t known yet, complete eel farming is difficult.
Even now, research on complete eel farming is being continued, and it is said that it may be successful with a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-15: Family reunion</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-15/</guid>
      <description>Today I came back to my parent&amp;rsquo;s home. Because my brother who lives in America was going back to my parent&amp;rsquo;s home. We had happy family reunion on Father&amp;rsquo;s day.
But there was also sad news. My brother&amp;rsquo;s wife&amp;rsquo;s father had stomach cancer and colon cancer. He had surgery to remove his cancer, and had been in the hospital for a month. It was last December. He didn&amp;rsquo;t inform his daughter that he had surgery so as not to make her worry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-14: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 09:47:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-14/</guid>
      <description>Today, I attneded AWS Summit Tokyo 2019: the final day. I used the Shonan Liner and the limited express Wakashio this morning, too. It was so comfortable that I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine coming to Kaihin Makuhari without getting on the express.
Keynote (10:00-11:30) It was the almost same as the Day 1&amp;rsquo;s keynote. Furthermore, the presenter talked too much and it was overtime. Panasonic&amp;rsquo;s speech wasn&amp;rsquo;t good neither.
[] AWS  (12:00-12:40) The presenter talked very well, so I could understand about the AWS Container Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-13: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-13/</guid>
      <description>Continuing from yesterday, I attended AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 today, too. This morning I used the Shonan Liner and the limited express Wakashio, so it was comfortable to come to the Kaihin-Makuhari station.
AWS Sumerian (10:00-10:40) AWS Sumerian provides Environments of development and distribution for eXtended Reality(XR). XR represents Virtual Reality(VR), Augmented Reality(AR), and Mixed Reality(MR). A presenter said that the XR Application developed by Sumerian works on various environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-12: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day1</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 09:44:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-12/</guid>
      <description>I attended AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 today. It will be held in 3 days. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna attend it every days.
Keynote (10:00-11:30) The music was loud at the venue and it was like rock concert, so I was a little excited. The opening of keynote was started with movies and dance. It&amp;rsquo;s completely concert.
In this AWS Summit Tokyo 2019, 33,000+ have been registered. AWS has 50% share in cloud business, it&amp;rsquo;s great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-11: Bufferin</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-11/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I have had chills, headache and runny nose. Maybe I had a cold, so I took Bufferin Ex. It cured me, as I expected. I&amp;rsquo;m very well today.
It&amp;rsquo;s said that half of Bufferin is made of tenderness. I wonder I was starving for ternderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-10: Friends</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-10/</guid>
      <description>Today I watched Friends after a long time, because I thought that I could learn daily conversation by wathing this movie.
In NETFLIX, I can download its movies, so I can watch them during commuting.
To learn daily conversation, I will watch it twice each time. The first time, I watch it in Japanese with English caption to know what each its quotes mean. The second time, I watch it in English with English caption, so I learn pronunciation and expressions in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-09: NETFLIX</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-09/</guid>
      <description>I registered to NETFLIX, because it displays movie&amp;rsquo;s caption in English. To study English in a fun way, it&amp;rsquo;s good for me to watch movies in English. My favorite movie is &amp;ldquo;You vs. Wild&amp;rdquo; featuring Bear Grylls.
NETFLIX is free for the first month, so during the period I will try to find out if NETFLIX is useful to studying English.
I like movies very much, so &amp;ldquo;what one likes, one will do well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-08: I&#39;m stoked about surfing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-08/</guid>
      <description>Today, I surfed in this morning and this evening. The waves size are from shoulder to head, it&amp;rsquo;s high for me. It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to getting out to out-side.
I rode waves only a few times, and wiped out many times. The sea is fairly cold that I might caught a bit cold. Still, I enjoyed surfing very much and I will keep surfing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-07: Master of Life</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 23:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-07/</guid>
      <description>My goal through my life is to be a &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo;. The word, &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo;, was told in the comic &amp;ldquo;Master Keaton&amp;rdquo;.
&amp;ldquo;Master of life&amp;rdquo; is a person who lives life in his own way and always has the life of his own colour. &amp;ldquo;Master Keaton vol.7&amp;rdquo; Chapter 3, page.79
It&amp;rsquo;s my goal, but I have not reached there at all. But I believe I will be able to become &amp;ldquo;master of life&amp;rdquo; someday, if I can continue studying for a lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-06: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</guid>
      <description>I use a textbook &amp;ldquo;TOUCHSTONE 2nd edition Student&amp;rsquo;s Book Level 3&amp;rdquo; in my English lesson. It&amp;rsquo;s at the low intermediate CFER level (A2-B1).
The followings are the homework I have to do by tomorrow.
page.5: Lesson-B 3.C Who do you admire ? I admire my brother.
Why ? Because, he works as a engineer in America. I also want to work as a engineer in America or Europe. I envy him working abroad and I&amp;rsquo;m proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-05: The English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</guid>
      <description>I took an English conversation lesson, it&amp;rsquo;s the first time I came back from my honeymoon.
I have visited England, Scotland, Canada and America in my honeymoon, so I thought that my English skill improve a little bit maybe, but it&amp;rsquo;s not at all.
I will study English harder than before so I can work abroad. Of course, I want to enjoy studying English. The proverb says, &amp;ldquo;what one likes, one will do well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-02: Start Learning python</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 19:32:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-02/</guid>
      <description>I bought this class a year ago, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t been studying python so much recently. I&amp;rsquo;ll try learning python again for improving my programming skill.
This class is very good and reasonable price. I think it fits people who want to study python for the first time. Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s fun for me to study python. I&amp;rsquo;ll learn python in a fun way from now on.
The progress of studying python is managed by the following github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-01: Jogging</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:14:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-01/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to surf if the waves were high, but today the waves were too small to surf.
I have jogged along Shonan Coast for the first time in two weeks this evening.
The weather was a bit cloudy, but it was very nice.
I think I have to do exercise, because I have been gaining weight from before, I will continue to jog from now on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-31: AWS DeepRacer League Workshop</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:10:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</guid>
      <description>AWS DeepRace League - Technical Workdshop Yesterday, I joined the &amp;ldquo;AWS Deep Racer League - Technical Workhop&amp;rdquo;, because I wanted to have fun learning about machine learning. The AWS DeepRacer is a 1&amp;frasl;18 scale racing car and it makes it possible to learn Reinforcement Learning (RL) in a fun way. It was disappointing that the hands-on was disabled due to a failure of the AWS service.
The presenter explained DeepRacer&amp;rsquo;s Reinforcement Learning and its simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-30: Surfed for the first time in two years</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 08:17:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I surfed for the first time in two years. The waves were waist high and very good for me. The water temperature was still a little cold and I needed a wetsuit.
Surfing after a long time was very pleasant and fun, I felt like going to keep surfing from now on.
This is the surfboard I used. It&amp;rsquo;s the Softech&amp;rsquo;s soft-surfboard: SALLY FITZGIBBONS SIGNATURE 7&amp;rsquo;0&amp;rdquo;. This long, buoyant surfboard is good for me because I am not strong and underexercised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-29: A TED talk that impressed me</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 07:48:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to build your confidence - and spark it others&amp;rdquo; I lose my confidence when I fail and disappointed myself,
when I was given cold stares, when I was blamed, and
when I was ignored.
This TED talk, Ms. Brittany Packnett&amp;rsquo;s speech, gives me a confidence.
It tells me that I need not lose my confidence.
Impressed words  Confidence is the necessary spark before everything that follows. Permission births confidence, community nurtures it and curiosity affirms it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-19: Honeymoon Day4</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/posts/2019-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/posts/2019-04-19/</guid>
      <description>Today, we went to Buckingham Palace to see changing of the guard. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen that before on TV. There was crowded so much. A lot of tourists came to see that like us. We saw changing the guard, they were like toy soldiers. After that, we went to British Museum to see Rosetta Stone. I was very impressed because it was the key to solving the mysteries of ancient Egypt. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-18: Honeymoon Day3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-18/</guid>
      <description> English Breakfast I ate English breakfast in England for the first time. It was lovely delicious.
Afternoon tea At last I had an afternoon tea in England. The tea is lovely tasty, and scones with plenty of clotted cream too. I enjoyed the afternoon tea.
Timeline </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-17: Honeymoon Day2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-17/</guid>
      <description>Take a walk in London We had a little bit jet lag, so we were going to relax and take a walk in London. And we&amp;rsquo;d like to buy gifts in return.
London is a huge and advanced city, however, London has buildings from the Middle Ages. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing and attractive city.
Shopping We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what to buy as gifts yet, so we were going to go window-shopping at Soho and Regent Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1 in London</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</guid>
      <description>Immigration I got a little bit nervous at immigration, because I usually get asked many questions at the immigration examination and I can&amp;rsquo;t answer well.
This time, however, immigration officers are very kind. Moreover, my wife said &amp;ldquo;This is our honeymoon&amp;rdquo; then, they said to us &amp;ldquo;Conguraturations!&amp;rdquo; with smile.
Tube We went to the center of London city by Tube: it&amp;rsquo;s subway in London. To ride Tube, we bought Oyster card at the station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</guid>
      <description>The day before depature We decided to carry out our luggage by Sagawa Express to the Handea airport. The luggage was to be carried by the carrier the day before. Until the day I was very busy with packing.
That day I could not sleep much because of excitement.
The depature day, at the airport The plane we were to ride was at 11:35. We wanted to arrive at the airport two hours ago, so we left home at 7:30.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>