<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>review on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:30:29 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-04: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:30:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-04/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned to soften comments and make sentences using those phrases. And I tried to continue speaking for one minute about something theme.
I sometimes couldn&#39;t find my words, however, I almost could continue speaking. It was prepared theme in advance, not free theme, though. My teacher, Cathay said that I prepared every lessons in advance and it was good, but I prepared too much, though. She meant that I only studied a few situations that the book described.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-03: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:20:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-03/</guid>
      <description>I learned softening comments using &amp;ldquo;I think&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;a little bit&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;maybe&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;kind of&amp;rdquo;, etc. In addition, I made some sentences with those expressions to soften. I mostly made it, however, I couldn&#39;t respond quickly, though.
I&#39;ll practice more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-28: Review the yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-28/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I practiced to continue speaking for one minute. In addition, I practiced to use some common phrasal verbs and various conjunctions. It was difficult to build my opinion, and use phrasal verbs and various conjunctions at the same time. I couldn&#39;t find any words and use those phrasal verbs and conjunctions very much.
On the other hand, the phrasal verbs and various conjunctions like those are important to casual conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-24: Review the yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-24/</guid>
      <description>I learned some vocabularies and grammars about dating. And I learned some phrasal verbs like get along, go out, break up and so on.
In addition, I learned elope and burn bridge. &amp;ldquo;Elope&amp;rdquo; means to leave from your home to get married even though your parents don&#39;t allow you to do that. And &amp;ldquo;burn bridge&amp;rdquo; means that you can&#39;t get back once you&#39;ve done that.
I tried to speak for one minute about anything, but I couldn&#39;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-21: Review the yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-21/</guid>
      <description>I learned relative clauses, who, that, and which. And I made some sentences about my friends using relative clauses. Moreover, I learned some vocabularies to remember.
 sit across: opposite side  She sits across a desk from me at work.   freak: crazy  You aren&#39;t a chips freak what you used to be. I&#39;m still a fried freak though.   meet through: via, because of  I have my British friend who I met through my wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-17: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-17/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I reviewed Unit 4 to 6 through some exercises. It&#39;s about ways to talk about the future and food. Again I tried to get off the phone, I didn&#39;t do well though. I couldn&#39;t end the conversation smoothly and naturally.
I finished Unit 4 to 6 at last, so next lesson, I&#39;m going to begin Unit 7 about relationships. I&#39;m little worried whether I can do well, because I&#39;m introverted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-10: Review and my department transfer</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</guid>
      <description>At yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned to build sentences using common collocations with do, make, and etc. In addition, I reviewed unit 4 to 6 through some exercises. I could respond some questions quickly rather than before, relatively. I used too many times &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; as conjunctions, though. I will use vary conjunctions next lesson.
At last I&#39;ll be transferred to new department. I&#39;m gonna work in the Cloud development team. I don&#39;t have to move a office, just 5 meters move in the same office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-07: Review the yesterday&#39;s English lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 12:17:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-07/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I answered a question whose the person couldn&#39;t have time to listen to recordings of his lectures. My advice was taking notes of his lectures, because it doesn&#39;t take time rather than listening to the recordings.
And I learned the meanings of &amp;ldquo;on the good side&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;undecided&amp;rdquo;. And &amp;ldquo;make a difference&amp;rdquo; has positive meanings, not negative. And you can use &amp;ldquo;make a &amp;lsquo;some adjective&amp;rsquo; impression&amp;rdquo;, for example good, bad, intense, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-24: Review the yesterday&#39;s English lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-24/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I practiced delivering my experience and making a question. I couldn&#39;t respond quickly, and I took time to deliver my experience. It was difficult to organize thoughts first before delivering. I felt I had to respond quickly, on the contrary I couldn&#39;t find my words. Or I found only meaning less words.
Calm down, chill out, take it easy, Naoki. Nobody blame you. You don&#39;t have to feel nervous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-21: Review of the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-21/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I practiced Unit.6 Free talk again. And I read the blog and summarized it.
At the previous lesson, I couldn&#39;t keep discussing about a community event. This time I did. I was relieved to be able to do that. I was a bit nervous before the last lesson. But I did and I got a bit confidence about English conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-15: Today&#39;s English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 20:57:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Today&#39;s English lesson, I practiced phone conversation, and meeting conversation about a community event. I tried that, however, I couldn&#39;t do well at all. I think, it&#39;s difficult for me to build my opinion and explain it in English at the same time. I do think in Japanese, and translate it into English. So, I can&#39;t respond quickly in English about a theme which I&#39;ve never think about. I&#39;ve read books about how to study English before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson.
I learned about the difference between assertive and aggressive. Assertive means that you are confident and say clearly what you think or what you want without attacking someone. It&#39;s polite and positive. Aggressive also means confident and saying clearly, but it has negative meaning like attacking someone.
And, I learned about phone conversation. When you call someone, first, you&#39;ve got to say greetings: Hi, Hello, etc. Second, you have to introduce yourself to the person on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&#39;ve got to learn those.
And I&#39;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&#39;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-18: it&#39;s rainy today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</guid>
      <description>In yesterday English lesson, I had my teacher check my blog again and reviewed Unit-4, and then finished it. And I started to learn Unit-5 and found that my teacher eats crisps too much.
I learned the following vocabularies.
 philanthropist  I told my teacher about my uncle who is keen on volunteering and then my teacher called him a philanthropist.   divorce and annulment  I didn&#39;t know the word annulment, and so I can&#39;t understand the difference between divorce and annulment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>