<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>review on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-24: Review the yesterday&#39;s English lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-24/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I practiced delivering my experience and making a question. I couldn&#39;t respond quickly, and I took time to deliver my experience. It was difficult to organize thoughts first before delivering. I felt I had to respond quickly, on the contrary I couldn&#39;t find my words. Or I found only meaning less words.
Calm down, chill out, take it easy, Naoki. Nobody blame you. You don&#39;t have to feel nervous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-21: Review of the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-21/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I practiced Unit.6 Free talk again. And I read the blog and summarized it.
At the previous lesson, I couldn&#39;t keep discussing about a community event. This time I did. I was relieved to be able to do that. I was a bit nervous before the last lesson. But I did and I got a bit confidence about English conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-15: Today&#39;s English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 20:57:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Today&#39;s English lesson, I practiced phone conversation, and meeting conversation about a community event. I tried that, however, I couldn&#39;t do well at all. I think, it&#39;s difficult for me to build my opinion and explain it in English at the same time. I do think in Japanese, and translate it into English. So, I can&#39;t respond quickly in English about a theme which I&#39;ve never think about. I&#39;ve read books about how to study English before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson.
I learned about the difference between assertive and aggressive. Assertive means that you are confident and say clearly what you think or what you want without attacking someone. It&#39;s polite and positive. Aggressive also means confident and saying clearly, but it has negative meaning like attacking someone.
And, I learned about phone conversation. When you call someone, first, you&#39;ve got to say greetings: Hi, Hello, etc. Second, you have to introduce yourself to the person on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&#39;ve got to learn those.
And I&#39;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&#39;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-18: it&#39;s rainy today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-18/</guid>
      <description>In yesterday English lesson, I had my teacher check my blog again and reviewed Unit-4, and then finished it. And I started to learn Unit-5 and found that my teacher eats crisps too much.
I learned the following vocabularies.
 philanthropist  I told my teacher about my uncle who is keen on volunteering and then my teacher called him a philanthropist.   divorce and annulment  I didn&#39;t know the word annulment, and so I can&#39;t understand the difference between divorce and annulment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>