<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ramen on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/ramen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ramen on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/ramen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-11-12: the presentation</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-11-12/</guid>
      <description>I have teamed up with three others for three months to tackle the training exercise about Machine Learning. Today, I went to Osaka to give the presentation about its results. I think that it was successful because we could answer some questions and the audience responded well. I submit the report and the source codes in a month, the training will be completed.
However, I must use what I learned in the training for my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-22: A one-day business trip to Osaka</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Today, I went to Osaka to get a lecture of AI.
I always buy the following this.
It&#39;s the most famous steamed bun with meat filling in Japan, especially in Kansai region. I stayed in the line for about twenty minutes to buy it.
And then, I ate the following this because I had enough time before the departure of the Shinkansen.
It&#39;s also famous ramen in Kansai region. The last time I ate it was when I was a graduate student, about 15 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-22: a relaxing day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-22/</guid>
      <description>Today is a relaxing day.
I woke up at 10:00 o&#39;clock on a late morning than usual. And then, I sent the packages which at the post office.
I had Taiwan ramen of a restaurant called Misen which is famouse in Nagoya for lunch. It was very hot and tasted wonderful.
After lunch, I took a nap for 1 hour. I went to surfing. The waves wasn&#39;t very high, but at least it was just right for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>