<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Touchstone-3 on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/touchstone-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Touchstone-3 on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:35:44 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/touchstone-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-28: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28-ts3-unit10-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:35:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28-ts3-unit10-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.D: Reviews 1. Reading A. Do you ever read reviews before deciding to see a movie? Are the reviews usually accurate? Tell the class. I&amp;rsquo;ve read reviews before deciding to see a movie. However, The reviews aren&amp;rsquo;t usually accurate for me, they&amp;rsquo;re rather too much praise for the movie. So, I usually avoid reading any reviews before watching a movie.
B. Read the movie review and the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-25-ts3-unit10-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 18:54:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-25-ts3-unit10-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.C: I was wondering &amp;hellip; 3. Listening and strategies: Favors at work 1. Peter  P: Um, Excuse me. Do you have a minute? B: Sure, Um. Hold on, Peter. Let me just finish this email. B: All right. What can I do for you? P: Well. Do you know the report you ask me to do for tomorrow? B: Yes. P: Well, Um. I was wondering if I could have a little more time to work on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-21-ts3-unit10-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:30:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-21-ts3-unit10-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.C: I was wondering &amp;hellip; A. What kinds of favors might you ask a teacher for? I have asked my teacher to extend the deadline.
B. What favor does Jake ask his professor? Does his professor agree? Jake asks his professor for writing a reference by next Monday, because he&amp;rsquo;s been applying for jobs.
His professor agree with that, as long as Jake brings the information his professor needs at late afternoon tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-18-ts3-unit10-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:57:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-18-ts3-unit10-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.B: Movies 1. Building vocabulary Delicatessen It&amp;rsquo;s a black comedy film directed by Jean-Pierre Jeunet and Marc Caro. Jean-Pierre Jeunet directed The City of Lost Children, Alien 2 Resurrection, and Amelie. Dominique Pinon plays a major character in the movie. He played in Alien 4 and in mostly Jean-Pierre Jeunet&amp;rsquo;s film.
I saw it when I was in a junior high school. At that time, I was a movie freak, so I used to go to rental video shop and borrowed 2 or 3 video tape every weekends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-07: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-ts3-unit10-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-ts3-unit10-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.A: Catching up 1. Getting started A. What kinds of things do people talk about when they are catching up with friends? Make a list.  About what changes have happened since the last time they met.  health job hobby family friends sports    B. Listen. What topics do the people above talk about? Were the topics on your list? 1. Bob &amp;amp; Louis Bob and Louis are talking about their recent state, especially work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-02: Touchstone-3 Unit-10</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-unit10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-unit10/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.A  Talk about your news using the present perfect, present perfect continuous, &amp;lsquo;since&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;for&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;in&amp;rsquo;.  Lesson.B  Describe movies Talk about your social life using the present perfect with &amp;lsquo;already&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;still&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;yet&amp;rsquo;.  Lesson.C  Ask for a favor politely Use &amp;lsquo;All right&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;OK&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;Sure&amp;rsquo; to agree to requests and &amp;lsquo;All right&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;OK&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;So&amp;rsquo; to change topic.  Lesson.D  Read a movie review Write a review  Pictures  There is a man who is playing bowling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-02: Touchstone-3 Checkpoint Units 7-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-checkpoint-units7-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-checkpoint-units7-9/</guid>
      <description>1. How many words can you remember? A. How many different phrasal verbs can you used to complete the sentences below?  What can you say about relationships?  You can go out with someone who you want to be with. You can get along with someone who you have to be with. You can split up with someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t like. You can break up with someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t want to be with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Free talk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-27-ts3-unit9-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-27-ts3-unit9-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Etiquette means the formal rules for polite behavior in society or in a particular group.
Free talk: Technology etiquette 1. Taking phone calls when you&amp;rsquo;re with friend  It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly fine to have a long conversation on your phone when you&amp;rsquo;re out with a friend.  I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the problem is. It&amp;rsquo;s no problem, provided that your friend allows you to take the call, or it&amp;rsquo;s urgent and important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-25-ts3-unit9-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:17:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-25-ts3-unit9-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.D: Identity theft Most People know how to stay safe in the city: Don&amp;rsquo;t walk alone after dark, hold onto your bag on crowded subways, and only ride in registered cabs. However, many people are not so savvy when it comes to staying safe on the Internet and don&amp;rsquo;t know what to look for. Identity theft - when thieves steal your personal information and use your identity to open bank or credit card accounts or take out home loans in your name -is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-20-ts3-unit9-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 18:12:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-20-ts3-unit9-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.D: Identity theft 1. Reading A. What is identity theft? What can happen when someone steals your identity? B. Read the magazine article. What scams does it describe? How do they work? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-17-ts3-unit9-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-17-ts3-unit9-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.C: On the other hand, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: You know what I mean?  It seems to me that every student should have a laptop in school.   Kids need to know how to use them. You know what I&amp;rsquo;m saying? Maybe, on the other hand, they can be distracting. So, school should set internet filter like parental control.  I don&amp;rsquo;t think you can listen to music and study at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.B: How things work 4. Building vocabulary making short paragraph using link word Title: live with Alexa
I live with Alexa. Six Alexas are on standby. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to set it up, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to look through the manual. All you have to do are to plug it in, hook it up with your wireless network, and to register your amazon account into it. If you register your google calendar into it, you can see your schedule on Alexa which has a display, or you can know your schedule when you ask Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.C: On the other hand, &amp;hellip; 1. Conversation strategy: Giving different opinions A. What kinds of online games do people play? Do you or your friends play them? People play a role-playing game, shooting game, fighting game, football game, or something. I don&amp;rsquo;t play online games now, but I had played online games for a while. It was a first-person shooter and I was killed so many times, because other players was too strong for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-09-ts3-unit9-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-09-ts3-unit9-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.B: How things work 1. Building language A. Listen. What problem is Ken having? Practice the conversation. Ken is having a cable problem of a gaming box.
B. Circle the two correct choices in each question. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner. I wrote my answers on my textbook&amp;hellip;
4. Building vocabulary C. Discuss the things below. Think of three&amp;hellip;  Different things you turn on every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-06-ts3-unit9-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 15:12:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-06-ts3-unit9-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A: Tech support 2. Grammar: Questions within sentences A. Rewrite these sentences. Start with the expressions given.  Are there any useful new app for students? Do you know &amp;hellip;   Do you know if there are any useful new apps for students?  Whare are the most popular sites for streaming movies? I wonder &amp;hellip;   I wonder what the most popular sites are for streaming movies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-02: Touchstone-3 Unit-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-02-ts3-unit9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-02-ts3-unit9/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A  Talk about problems with technology using questions within sentences.  Lesson.B  Describe how things work using separable phrasal verbs like turn on and plug in. Ask for help with technology using how to + verb, where to + verb, etc.  Lesson.C  Give different opinions with expressions like On the ohter hand Use You know what I mean? to ask someone to agree with you  Lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31-ts3-unit9-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:45:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31-ts3-unit9-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A: Tech support 1. Getting started A. What kinds of problems do people have with their computers? Make a class list.  Data is gone. Disk is full. It&amp;rsquo;s shut down suddenly. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t show anything on a display. It can&amp;rsquo;t access to Internet. It can&amp;rsquo;t print out. You can&amp;rsquo;t send or receive an e-mail. You can&amp;rsquo;t access to a certain web page. You can&amp;rsquo;t use a mouse device or a keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-28: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Free talk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28-ts3-unit8-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28-ts3-unit8-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Free talk: 8.What would you do? 1. If you had an hour to spare right now, what would you do? If I had an hour to spare right now, I would take a nap. Because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well last night. I wake up at 3 am in these days, I don&amp;rsquo;t have no idea. And I sometimes can&amp;rsquo;t sleep again.
2. If you had one month of free time, what would you do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-22: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-22-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-22-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 2. Speaking and writing: What would you change? A. If you Had last year to live over again, what would you change? Think of answers to the questions, and make notes below. Is there &amp;hellip;
 a place you&amp;rsquo;d go more often?  I would go surfing more often. Last year, I didn&amp;rsquo;t go surfing so much. Because, I hurt right hip joint and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have warm wet suits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-19: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-19-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:16:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-19-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 1. Reading D. Discuss these questions 1. What have been the most important things in the writer&amp;rsquo;s life?  to be relaxed and live peacefully. to try new things and enjoy them. to be respected by others&amp;hellip;. his or her family and friends to spend time on something worth, like exciting experiences, visiting around the world like that. to enjoy life without worry.  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-13-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-13-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 1. Reading A. What kinds of things do people regret in life? Make a class list. I think&amp;hellip; Some people wish they had got married with another partner. Because some Japanese husband and wife are always complaining about their partner.
And, Someone who had a car accident wishes he had paid more attention, I think. Especially someone is still suffering from the aftereffects of the car accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: That would be &amp;hellip;  If you could do something really different, what would you do?   I&amp;rsquo;d fly to the moon if I could. I want to walk on the moon once. It&amp;rsquo;s like bouncing on the trampoline, I guess. It must be fun.  If you could have any job, what would you do?   Marine biologist and fish farmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-04: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:45:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 1. Conversation strategy: Giving advice A. What tough decisions have you made? Did you ask for advice? Tell the class. I had made tough decision to go to which grad school. One of them was Osaka University where I got bachelor degree, Another one was NARA Institute of Science and Technology(NAIST).
Osaka University is in the urban city and you can go to center of Osaka city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-02: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:23:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of asking about imaginary situations or events. I answered the notebook&amp;rsquo;s questions and made a question using &amp;ldquo;what would do &amp;hellip;, if &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Furthermore, I learned words below.
 diabetes  a serious disease in which there is too much sugar in your blood   charge you for &amp;hellip;  to ask someone for particular amount of money for something your are selling   keep them  take them   waning  when the moon wanes, you gradually see less of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-28: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:26:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about dilemmas and some verbs + prepositions. Dilemma means a situation in which it&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to decide what to do, because all the choices seem equally good or equally bad. Longman dictionary says that. I answered questions which have dilemmas.
And today, I worked from home all day. It&amp;rsquo;s due to avoid infecting with corona virus. My company told all employees not to work at the office as possible as they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:38:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.B: Life&amp;rsquo;s little dilemmas 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. Listen and take the quiz. Circle your answers. Then compare with a partner.  b   It&amp;rsquo;s depends on the friend, I mean that it depends on the closeness with the friend. If the friend is one of my best friends, I never let the friend buy a new one. But unless the friend is my best friend, I would let the friend pay for it, definitely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 21:02:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of wishes and imaginary situations or events. And I made some sentences with wishes and imaginary situations. Furthermore, I started lesson B about dilemmas. I made some sentences which have dilemmas, however I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do well. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t feel dilemmas, I live simply every day, I guess.
Anyway, at the next lesson, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna continue to learn about dilemmas. My homework is to make some sentences about my dilemmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 3. Listening and speaking: Just one wish  He wishes he could just sit down and watch TV.   Because he needs to do laundry.  She wishes she went out more with her friends.   Because She can&amp;rsquo;t afford to go out more.  He wishes he could get together with his family more often.   Because He doesn&amp;rsquo;t live near his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 1. Getting started A. What would you like more of in your life? I can&amp;rsquo;t speak English smoothly and naturally. So I wish I could speak English well. If I could speak English well, I could enjoy movies, musical, and trip more than before, definitely. Furthermore, if I do that, I&amp;rsquo;d get a interesting job and work happily. And if I win a lottery, I&amp;rsquo;d probably take long vacations to go all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-8</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Description about the pictures 1 There is an doctor and a nurse. They are in a hospital room. They smile with confidence, as I see it.
2. There is a rich house with a garden and a convertible car. A rich family live there, I guess.
3. There is an old man and an old lady, their children and grand children. It&amp;rsquo;s a celebration to mark the forty or fifty anniversary of their marriage, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 3. Writing: Your circle of friends A. Think about three of your friends. Tell a partner about them. Discuss the questions below.  What is your friend like? How did you meet? Why did you become friends? What do you have in common? What do you do together?  B. Read the article below and the Help note. Then write an article like the one page 66 about your circle of friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 2. Speaking and listening: Getting back in touch  His college friends   G: So what are you doing this weekend, Javier? J: Oh, I have to do something around my house.  You know, do the laundry, go food shopping, the kind of stuff. How about you?   G: Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go see the new science fiction movie that&amp;rsquo;s playing downtown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-05: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:44:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 1. Reading A. What are some good ways to make new friends? Make a list.  Join new community, club or something.. Ask your friends to introduce someone to you. Do something new. Go some places where you have never been. Be friendly for strangers. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to talk to strangers. Talking with smile and laughing happily. Don&amp;rsquo;t complain or blame someone, I mean you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say negative things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.C: She&amp;rsquo;s just a bit odd. 1. Conversation strategy: Softening comments A. What are your neighbors like? Do you get along with them? Tell the class. My neighbors next door are a man and his daughter. It seems to me that they get along well, because I sometimes see they&amp;rsquo;re talking with smile. But late at night once or twice, I heard him to shout like being drunk, so I&amp;rsquo;m bit worried about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Before starting Lesson C. I will do homework about Lesson B.
Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B, Section.2 A.7-9 7. First dates usually turn out to be a disaster! I agree with that partially. Not usually, sometimes it turns out to be a disaster. Because someone who don&amp;rsquo;t know each other may not be able to have a nice chat at the first date. The person don&amp;rsquo;t know what the another person like and don&amp;rsquo;t like, so that sometimes the person do something what the another person don&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B: Dating 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. High school sweethearts I have some questions about vocabularies.
&amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;work out&amp;rdquo; emphasizes this expression? If this statement doesn&amp;rsquo;t use &amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo;, does it have the same meanings?
What does &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; mean? I think that there is an inconsistency between &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo;. Because &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; means the current and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; means the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 18:17:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.A: Circle of friends 1. Getting started A. Where do people make friends? How many places can you think of? Make a list. I think people make friends at school, workplace, clubs, and introducing from friends.
 school an introduction from friends workplace sports club  B. Listen and read the article above. How did Christopher meet his friends? He met his friends at college and work, or through his friends, and near his home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Checkpoint</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</guid>
      <description>4. What&amp;rsquo;s going to happen?  Cindy: What time does your train leave (leave)today? Dana: I &amp;rsquo;m gonna take (take)the 3:30 train. Oh, no, it&amp;rsquo;s almost 3:00! Cindy: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry. I &amp;rsquo;ll drive (drive)you to the station. Dana: Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to do that. I will call (call)a taxi. Cindy: No way! I can take you. I &amp;rsquo;m gonna go (go)to the mall this afternoon. It&amp;rsquo;s not far from the train station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 page.62</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-09-ts3-unit6-p62/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-09-ts3-unit6-p62/</guid>
      <description>Vocabulary notebook 2. Write sentences to help you remember these expressions. Do some thinking I&amp;rsquo;m doing some thinking. But I have no idea.
Do something fun I want to do something fun. But I can&amp;rsquo;t make up my mind to do surfing, camping, or traveling.
Do volunteer work I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do volunteer work now. Because I&amp;rsquo;m really busy for work.
Make a decision I made a decision that affected my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 2.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</guid>
      <description>D. Read the Help note. Then read the question and answer with as long as, provided that, or unless. Question I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more organized, so I decided to record my lectures, but I never have time to watch them. Any ideas?
Answer You can&amp;rsquo;t remember what you learned, unless you review your lectures. So, you ought to find time to review your lectures, however, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to watch the recordings - provided that you remember the key points of your lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&amp;rsquo;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1. Reading A. Do you ever multitask? What kinds of things do you do at the same time? Is multitasking a good thing to do? About 20 years ago, when I was at network operation team in the previous company, I sometimes did multitask.
When I was in a network trouble, I&amp;rsquo;ve done multitask. It was calling customer, solving the problems, writing the report, asking my colleague to help me by a chat tool, and explaining that to my boss at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-12: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson C: I&amp;rsquo;ve got to get going. 1. Conversation strategy: Ending phone conversations A. When was the last time you were running late? Why? It was last Saturday, because I was going to be late for a appointment of the dental clinic. My appointment was 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock, but I woke up 9:35. The dental clinic is a 5 minutes away by bicycle. So, I had to get ready to go out in 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-09-ts3-unit6-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-09-ts3-unit6-b/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson B: Problems and solutions  2. Extra practice (p.145) A.1. I&amp;rsquo;d prefer not to move out of my apartment. I&amp;rsquo;d rather not to move out of my apartment.
A.2. I should really learn to drive. I&amp;rsquo;m really going to have tolearn to drive.
A.3. I should save some money to buy a car. I ought tosave some money to buy a car.
A.4. I think you should talk to your boss about a promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
