<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>common vocabulary on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/common-vocabulary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in common vocabulary on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/common-vocabulary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-26: Ophthalmic clinic again</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-26/</guid>
      <description>Today I went to another ophthalmic clinic.
Two weeks ago, I went to a ophthalmic clinic, because I see a small circle for an instant in my right eye when I blink. It&#39;s a kind of shadow that I see after I see a bright small light. I was worried about my eyes, however, the doctor couldn&#39;t find the reason. The doctor said, &amp;ldquo;There is no problem now, come again a month later&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-16: A first ophthalmic clinic</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday, I went to a dental clinic, not for cleaning. It&#39;s for making mouthpiece. I sometimes grind my teeth while sleeping. It&#39;s for preventing from that. Cathy said that in Philippines we slap the person who grinds teeth in a sleep. Oh, my gosh. I won&#39;t tell that to my wife.
And I went to a ophthalmic clinic for the first time. I have never been to a ophthalmic clinic, because I have good eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-15: Today&#39;s English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 20:57:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Today&#39;s English lesson, I practiced phone conversation, and meeting conversation about a community event. I tried that, however, I couldn&#39;t do well at all. I think, it&#39;s difficult for me to build my opinion and explain it in English at the same time. I do think in Japanese, and translate it into English. So, I can&#39;t respond quickly in English about a theme which I&#39;ve never think about. I&#39;ve read books about how to study English before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&#39;ve got to learn those.
And I&#39;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&#39;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>