<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 15:59:51 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-09: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-09-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 15:59:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-09-news/</guid>
      <description>Climate change: Could the coronavirus crisis spur a green recovery? I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about Ms. Greta Thunberg, a environment activist, reading the article below.
 Climate change: Could the coronavirus crisis spur a green recovery?  The drop in traffic due to corona virus is a major contributor to the fall in planet-warming CO2 emissions we&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed globally. Most people think climate change is as serious as coronavirus.
So, people will try to avoid using public transport system for fear of infection, and a plan of building road will be quit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-08: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-08-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-08-news/</guid>
      <description>I read some articles below.
Where&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s spirit of tolerance came from I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about characteristics of city culture, reading the article below.
 Where&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s spirit of tolerance came from  San Francisco has always been known as a city of nonconformity. But in recent decades, already-outlandish San Francisco rents and everyday prices has been inflating and living costs has been pushed to 25% higher than the national average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-07: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 15:46:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-news/</guid>
      <description>I read the articles below. And I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about around Japan, especially China.
 コロナ後、世界秩序が変化　中国覇権強まる　ダリオ氏語る Global Backlash Builds Against China Over Coronavirus  A certain founder of the largest hedge fund in USA said that China will emerge as the dominant power in the world, because the US debt will expand and the value of the US dollar as the key currency will decline.
On the other hand, the New York Times said that global backlash builds against China for its initial mishandling of this crisis over corona virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-04: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-04-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 19:52:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-04-news/</guid>
      <description>I read the articles below. And I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about my job in the near future.
 IT系の雇用慣行続くか Jobs after coronavirus: The US labor market won&amp;rsquo;t bounce right back The U.S. economy has been hit hard by the coronavirus pandemic - here&amp;rsquo;s what it&amp;rsquo;s like for job seekers  The outbreak of COVID-19 reveals two things. Firstly, U.S.A collects IT engineers from around the world. Secondaly, IT startup company depends on gig workers who don&amp;rsquo;t have any public welfare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-04: Homework</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-04-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 15:29:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-04-homework/</guid>
      <description>I read a few news about airlines in a few days.
 Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s company Berkshire Hathaway sells US airline shares Buffett Dumps Airlines and His Aerospace Pain Will Only Worsen What happenes to airliens after the coronavirus crisis ends? Airlines Could Increase Ticket Prices After COVID-19 Lockdown  Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s company sold all of its shares in the four largest US airlines, Delta Air Lines, American Airlines, Southwest Airlines, and United Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>