<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 19:35:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-29: review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 19:35:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-29/</guid>
      <description>Today I worked from home.
At the last time, I learned showing I understand. And I practiced to respond using &amp;lsquo;must&amp;rsquo; in conversation.
And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna ask a question below to teacher. What does it mean? When do you use it?
 gotcha: interjection  a word meaning I&amp;rsquo;ve got you, used when you catch someone or trick them in some way a word meaning &amp;lsquo;I understand&amp;rsquo; look at possible gotchas when using deep learning in practice, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-29: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-29-ts3-unit11-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 14:15:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-29-ts3-unit11-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Lesson.C: That must be fun. 3. Listening and strategies: People and situations A. Listen to four conversations. Match each person with the situation he or she explains.  Mark: c Angela: d Linda: a Dave: b  B. Show you understand. Write a response to each person using &amp;lsquo;must&amp;rsquo;.  Mark  Hey, Mark. How are your tennis lessons going?   M: Oh, not too bad.   You&amp;rsquo;ve been taking lessons a couple of years now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-22: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-22-ts3-unit11-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-22-ts3-unit11-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Lesson.C: That must be fun. 1. Conversation strategy: Showing you understand A. What impressions do you get about Hal and Debra from the picture? Debra is interested in the saxophone. And Hal must be feeling exciting.
B. Listen. Why hasn&amp;rsquo;t Hal made much progress with his saxophone? Because he must be busy with his job in the morning and he must be tired after work.
summary
Debra found Hal&amp;rsquo;s saxophone in his office and she was interested in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-21-ts3-unit11-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-21-ts3-unit11-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Lesson.B: Ups and downs 3. Talk about it: Feelings Discuss the questions . Write down any intersting or unusual responses, and then tell the class.
 Do you know anyone who is annoying? Do you get annoyed with people often?  Yes, I know my colleague is annoying, because he is sarcastic. I say something, whatever it is, he says its&amp;rsquo; bad. Yes, I get annoyed with people often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-18: Air conditioning</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 18:30:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-18/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s drizzling and humid today. I turned on an air conditioner and worked from home. When I work at office, I can&amp;rsquo;t change the temperature of the air conditioner. It&amp;rsquo;s good to set my comfortable temperature.
news Recently I use an air conditioner during work and sleep. I feel that temperature has been increasing every year a kind of Japan might be changing to a tropical country. So, I&amp;rsquo;ve read this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-15: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-15-ts3-unit11-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-15-ts3-unit11-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Lesson.B: Ups and downs 1. Building vocabulary and grammar They might have a barbeque, however everybody must be interested in anything else, so I worry that meat mihght be burned.
There are several baloons. They&amp;rsquo;re looks good, but they might turn out to be garbage.
B. Look at the things people say below. How are they feeloing? Make guesses.  This movie&amp;rsquo;s too long.  He msut be bored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-15: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-15-ts3-unit11-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-15-ts3-unit11-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Lesson.A: Speculating 3. Grammer: Modal verbs for speculating B. What other guesses can you make about each picture? It must be a winter and it must not a tropical place there. She might be a ski player or a ice skater. Because she&amp;rsquo;s training on snow field. Otherwise, she might be a trail runner. A marathon runner can&amp;rsquo;t be training on snow field.
She must be feeling sad in a shoping mall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-14: Speaking up</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-14/</guid>
      <description>I had a class of English Speaking up just now. And the teacher suggested me a web site which helps me measure my English skill. It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Test Your Vocab&amp;rdquo;. I did it, and my score is 6,370 words. It can be enough to make a small talk in ordinary life, however I can&amp;rsquo;t. Because it&amp;rsquo;s just a number of words I can read, not speak. I should get more words I can use in having conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-13: Speaking up</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 12:41:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-13/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning English at English school for about a year. I want to improve my English more, however I sometimes can&amp;rsquo;t listen to what my teacher said, and even if I can, I can&amp;rsquo;t respond quickly.
In these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading some news and summarizing it. And I give a short speech about it in my class. Although, I can&amp;rsquo;t remember all of the speech, so I can&amp;rsquo;t give a speech well, I read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-12: Touchstone-3 Unit-11 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-12-ts3-unit11-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-12-ts3-unit11-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-11: Impressions Before you begin &amp;hellip; What impressions do you get from each of these pictures? Make some guesses.
 What do you think is the relationship between the people in each picture?  A coach and players of a football team A instructor and a beginner of sky diving A birthday girl, her siblings or friends, and her parents and grandparents.   What do you think is happening?  The football team won the championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-04: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-04-ts3-unit10-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:57:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-04-ts3-unit10-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.D: Reviews 1.D. Read the review and comments again  It was Titanic 12 years ago. Because people have an energy crisis on Earth. He feels sympathy for Na&amp;rsquo;vi. They are the computer-generated special effects, the music and Na&amp;rsquo;vi language. Its story might keep some people from seeing Avatar. Yes, they will. Sue-Ann said that.  2. Listening and writing: I&amp;rsquo;d really recommend it. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-06-01: June 1st. Rainy season is coming.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 18:34:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-06-01/</guid>
      <description>Rainy season is coming. It comes 3 week earlier than usual year. Also mosquitoes is coming. I hate both. I can&amp;rsquo;t sleep at all hot and humid night with flying mosquitoes near my ears. It&amp;rsquo;s too irritating to keep sane.
So, I bought an insect repellant and insect killer at Costco in Zama city. Zama is little bit closer than Yokohama from Fujisawa. There was fewer people than usual at Costco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-31: HHKB</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 11:21:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-31/</guid>
      <description>I bought new keyboard. It makes me feeling exciting and comfortable. I can code programs quickly and comfortably with it. I can&amp;rsquo;t work at office any more. I bought display, keyboard, trackpad, and external GPU, and I tidied up my home network and my room. There is no reason to work at office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-28: Keep having English lessons online</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 19:11:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28/</guid>
      <description>English school where I have classes lifted restrictions of having online class. However, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep having English lesson online. Because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to ride crowded train and I&amp;rsquo;m little worry about having a class in a small booth.
Today I had online seminars about Amazon Web Services. It was interesting. Moreover, not only Amazon but also tech companies are going to hold various online seminars next month. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to those online classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-27: Knee riding</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-27/</guid>
      <description>Just like yesterday, I went to surfing after work. It was windy, so surface of the sea was bumpy and it was little difficult to ride waves.
In these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying knee-riding, which is way to ride on my knees on a surfboard. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to ride waves and I can enjoy to feel more waves. However, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a commonly way to ride waves. I know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-26: Surfing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-26/</guid>
      <description>I went to surfing this afternoon and evening. I enjoyed surfing from 5:30pm until little after 7:00pm. The days are getting longer in these days, so I can enjoy surfing a lot than before. It&amp;rsquo;s very good surfing after work. I feel tiring from work has gone. Actually I&amp;rsquo;m exhausted after surfing, though.
Anyway, since I started to work from home, I have time to free than before. So, I can enjoy everyday without stress from commuting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-22: Review the yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 19:02:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-22/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned how to use &amp;lsquo;I was wondering&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; to asking for a favor politely, and the difference between hope and wish. You can use wish when you think that it&amp;rsquo;s impossible and You can use hope when you think that it&amp;rsquo;s possible and it will be happened.
I have a homework. I have to make five sentences using common expressions which I use when I ask my colleagues for a favor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-18-ts3-unit10-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:57:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-18-ts3-unit10-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.B: Movies 1. Building vocabulary Delicatessen It&amp;rsquo;s a black comedy film directed by Jean-Pierre Jeunet and Marc Caro. Jean-Pierre Jeunet directed The City of Lost Children, Alien 2 Resurrection, and Amelie. Dominique Pinon plays a major character in the movie. He played in Alien 4 and in mostly Jean-Pierre Jeunet&amp;rsquo;s film.
I saw it when I was in a junior high school. At that time, I was a movie freak, so I used to go to rental video shop and borrowed 2 or 3 video tape every weekends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-17: it&#39;s a good day to surf</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-17/</guid>
      <description>It seemed that there was crowded around Enoshima-Island due to tourist. Everybody can&amp;rsquo;t stand self-quarantine any more, I guess. So, I avoided going to the beach due to infection with corona virus in the morning and around noon. I went surfing just before sunset. It was good saves to surf in the morning rather than around sunset, however, there was few surfers rather than morning, so that I could enjoy surfing much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-16: teeth and surf</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 15:24:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-16/</guid>
      <description>I had my teeth clean at dental clinic in the morning. I have been going to dental clinic to remove dental stone from my teeth every 2 or 3 months. Because teeth care and eye care are most important factors for quality of life. I want to trip all over the world and enjoy local speciality meals there, I want to see beautiful views and historical spot.
Moreover, physical fitness is also important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-07: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-ts3-unit10-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-07-ts3-unit10-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.A: Catching up 1. Getting started A. What kinds of things do people talk about when they are catching up with friends? Make a list.  About what changes have happened since the last time they met.  health job hobby family friends sports    B. Listen. What topics do the people above talk about? Were the topics on your list? 1. Bob &amp;amp; Louis Bob and Louis are talking about their recent state, especially work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-02: Touchstone-3 Unit-10</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-unit10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-unit10/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.A  Talk about your news using the present perfect, present perfect continuous, &amp;lsquo;since&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;for&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;in&amp;rsquo;.  Lesson.B  Describe movies Talk about your social life using the present perfect with &amp;lsquo;already&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;still&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;yet&amp;rsquo;.  Lesson.C  Ask for a favor politely Use &amp;lsquo;All right&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;OK&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;Sure&amp;rsquo; to agree to requests and &amp;lsquo;All right&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;OK&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;So&amp;rsquo; to change topic.  Lesson.D  Read a movie review Write a review  Pictures  There is a man who is playing bowling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-02: a lazy day 2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:33:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02/</guid>
      <description>I spent lazy time today just like I did yesterday. I woke up late, ate lunch, took a nap and studied little bit English. It&amp;rsquo;s too bad. To change my job, I should improve English and technical skill. I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to waste. I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t forget it and I always have to remember it. I have to live a regular life and keep studying during holidays. I&amp;rsquo;ll do it. I said it yesterday as well, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-02: Touchstone-3 Checkpoint Units 7-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-checkpoint-units7-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-02-ts3-checkpoint-units7-9/</guid>
      <description>1. How many words can you remember? A. How many different phrasal verbs can you used to complete the sentences below?  What can you say about relationships?  You can go out with someone who you want to be with. You can get along with someone who you have to be with. You can split up with someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t like. You can break up with someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t want to be with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-01: a lazy day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-01/</guid>
      <description>My holidays start. However, it&amp;rsquo;s not holiday in a sense because of corona virus. I could have stayed Cebu. If there isn&amp;rsquo;t corona virus, I could stay Cebu for studying English.
There is nothing for it but to avoid infecting with corona virus and study English at home. I&amp;rsquo;ll think about improving my English and technical skill during this holidays.
Still, I spent lazy time today. I studied little bit English, but I just ate and jogged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-30: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-30/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I studied vocabulary notebook about on and off. I reviewed phrasal verbs and made some sentences using phrasal verbs.
From tomorrow, my holidays are gonna start. However, unfortunately I can&amp;rsquo;t go anywhere due to corona virus. Most shops and restaurants are closed, and the local people might not welcome people who come from other places, because of suppressing infection of corona virus.
Now, very gloomy atmosphere is sweeping over Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-29: A new laptop</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-29/</guid>
      <description>Today, my new laptop was arrived. It&amp;rsquo;s new xps13 which has a 13.4 inches display and Ice-Lake chip and it&amp;rsquo;s superior to my laptop which I bought three and half years ago. I have felt little bit irritated about bad performance of my laptop, so I ordered it April 14th.
At first, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can receive it today because DELL told me it will be arribed May 18th. I think it&amp;rsquo;s super late, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Free talk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-27-ts3-unit9-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-27-ts3-unit9-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Etiquette means the formal rules for polite behavior in society or in a particular group.
Free talk: Technology etiquette 1. Taking phone calls when you&amp;rsquo;re with friend  It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly fine to have a long conversation on your phone when you&amp;rsquo;re out with a friend.  I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the problem is. It&amp;rsquo;s no problem, provided that your friend allows you to take the call, or it&amp;rsquo;s urgent and important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-25-ts3-unit9-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:17:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-25-ts3-unit9-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.D: Identity theft Most People know how to stay safe in the city: Don&amp;rsquo;t walk alone after dark, hold onto your bag on crowded subways, and only ride in registered cabs. However, many people are not so savvy when it comes to staying safe on the Internet and don&amp;rsquo;t know what to look for. Identity theft - when thieves steal your personal information and use your identity to open bank or credit card accounts or take out home loans in your name -is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-21: Review and today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 19:15:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-21/</guid>
      <description>Also today, I worked from home. I did some stretching exercises this morning and yesterday&amp;rsquo;s morning after waking up. Then, I can get through the day comfortably. I&amp;rsquo;ll continue to do stretching after waking up.
I had an English lesson yesterday. It was a remote lesson via zoom, video call. I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten used to have a remote lesson, I think. However I&amp;rsquo;ll have a offline lesson if I can. There is a good point on a offline lesson, that is I can see a teacher&amp;rsquo;s mouth behavior and hear clear pronunciation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-20-ts3-unit9-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 18:12:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-20-ts3-unit9-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.D: Identity theft 1. Reading A. What is identity theft? What can happen when someone steals your identity? B. Read the magazine article. What scams does it describe? How do they work? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-19: Surfing, book-off and surfing.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-19/</guid>
      <description>In the morning, I went surfing for the first time in a while. Because I bought a bodyboard and wanted to try it. Fortunately, there were good waves to surf. Unfortunately, I lost my right foot swim-fin. When I tried to ride a big wave and I caught it, however, on the contrary the wave caught me and swallowed me. I was swallowed, upside down, round and round. When I floated to the surface of the sea, I realized that my right swim-fin had gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-18: Review and today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 18:39:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-18/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I practiced linking words and learned expressions to have someone agree with me. Moreover, I talked about technology matters, what technology bring us, good things and bad things.
I was given homework to speak about movies what I&amp;rsquo;ve ever watched showed highest future technology. To be precise, What do you think is the peak of technology and provide similar movie about it. Do short presentation.
I remember some movies I&amp;rsquo;ve watched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-17-ts3-unit9-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-17-ts3-unit9-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.C: On the other hand, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: You know what I mean?  It seems to me that every student should have a laptop in school.   Kids need to know how to use them. You know what I&amp;rsquo;m saying? Maybe, on the other hand, they can be distracting. So, school should set internet filter like parental control.  I don&amp;rsquo;t think you can listen to music and study at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-16: Review and today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 17:37:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-16/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I practiced linking words and learned about giving different opinions using &amp;lsquo;I know what you mean, but&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Maybe. On the other hand, &amp;lsquo;,&amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. Don&amp;rsquo;t you think&amp;rsquo;, and so on.
I worked from home today, but I went to the office yesterday. Because I took a GPU box back from my workplace to home. I bought it last month and it was delivered to my workplace last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-13: Pollenosis</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I had a bad condition due to pollenosis. I had a terrible runny nose, so many sneeze, and feeling heavy. Fortunately, I had no cough. It should not be corona virus. Today I feel better and I could work from home.
In these days, I just work and jog. But in rainy day I can&amp;rsquo;t jog, it would be nice if there were enough waves to surf at least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.B: How things work 4. Building vocabulary making short paragraph using link word Title: live with Alexa
I live with Alexa. Six Alexas are on standby. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to set it up, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to look through the manual. All you have to do are to plug it in, hook it up with your wireless network, and to register your amazon account into it. If you register your google calendar into it, you can see your schedule on Alexa which has a display, or you can know your schedule when you ask Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-13-ts3-unit9-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.C: On the other hand, &amp;hellip; 1. Conversation strategy: Giving different opinions A. What kinds of online games do people play? Do you or your friends play them? People play a role-playing game, shooting game, fighting game, football game, or something. I don&amp;rsquo;t play online games now, but I had played online games for a while. It was a first-person shooter and I was killed so many times, because other players was too strong for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-12: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 07:55:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-12/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned about separable phrasal verbs, and practiced linking consonants and vowels.
I had a English lesson via video call for the first time. At first, I&amp;rsquo;ve got bewildered in unfamiliar remote lesson. However, several minutes later I got used to getting a remote lesson.
It&amp;rsquo;s sometimes noisy and unclear at a remote lesson, but it&amp;rsquo;s a good experience for a phone interview to change my job, I think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-09-ts3-unit9-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-09-ts3-unit9-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.B: How things work 1. Building language A. Listen. What problem is Ken having? Practice the conversation. Ken is having a cable problem of a gaming box.
B. Circle the two correct choices in each question. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner. I wrote my answers on my textbook&amp;hellip;
4. Building vocabulary C. Discuss the things below. Think of three&amp;hellip;  Different things you turn on every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-07: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 19:02:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-07/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned making questions within sentences. And I delivered my opinions about those questions. Moreover, I answered questions about the Internet.
I found that I can&amp;rsquo;t listen to link words as liaison. It seems to me that it&amp;rsquo;s a new word that I haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of. So, next lesson I&amp;rsquo;m gonna learn about link words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-9 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-06-ts3-unit9-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 15:12:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-06-ts3-unit9-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A: Tech support 2. Grammar: Questions within sentences A. Rewrite these sentences. Start with the expressions given.  Are there any useful new app for students? Do you know &amp;hellip;   Do you know if there are any useful new apps for students?  Whare are the most popular sites for streaming movies? I wonder &amp;hellip;   I wonder what the most popular sites are for streaming movies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-02: Touchstone-3 Unit-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-02-ts3-unit9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-02-ts3-unit9/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A  Talk about problems with technology using questions within sentences.  Lesson.B  Describe how things work using separable phrasal verbs like turn on and plug in. Ask for help with technology using how to + verb, where to + verb, etc.  Lesson.C  Give different opinions with expressions like On the ohter hand Use You know what I mean? to ask someone to agree with you  Lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-01: Cancelled a short-stay for learning English in Cebu</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-01/</guid>
      <description>I cancelled my short-stay for learning English in Cebu which I reserved two months ago. It&amp;rsquo;s due to corona virus. I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry for that. I really want to go to Cebu for learning English. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about how I improve my English skill during a long vacation in April and May. I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if I get online classes, too.
Furthermore, I started to learn for being a Data Scientist in English I&amp;rsquo;m gonna learn English in everything like studying tech and working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-9</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31-ts3-unit9-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:45:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31-ts3-unit9-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-9: Tech savvy? Lesson.A: Tech support 1. Getting started A. What kinds of problems do people have with their computers? Make a class list.  Data is gone. Disk is full. It&amp;rsquo;s shut down suddenly. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t show anything on a display. It can&amp;rsquo;t access to Internet. It can&amp;rsquo;t print out. You can&amp;rsquo;t send or receive an e-mail. You can&amp;rsquo;t access to a certain web page. You can&amp;rsquo;t use a mouse device or a keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-31: Corona virus killed the most famous comedian in Japan.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-31/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry for his death. He is the greatest and most loved comedian in Japan. I used to watch his comedy show every Saturday when I was a child. I think half of Japanese people watched his show at that time, especially kids including me loved him. I genuinely pray that his soul may rest in peace.
His death will save many Japanese, I guess. So far, many Japanese might think &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m OK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-29: Review and a diary</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:39:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-29/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s snowy today, so I carried my wife to her workplace. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna study English and Kubernetes today.
At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I discussed the questions. And I leaned the vocabularies below.
 carrier, asymptomatic  I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be a corona virus career. Because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to kill anyone. Even if I became a corona virus career, I might be an asymptomatic. However, if I carried corona virus to old guys, they might be died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-28: almost lockdown</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 15:50:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28/</guid>
      <description>I had worked from home in the last few days, same like last weeks. A governor asked citizens to avoid nonessential outings this weekend.
But I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go to have an English offline class. Of course, I can take it online, but I wanna do offline. To study English smoothly, offline class is important. There are time gap and I can&amp;rsquo;t see teacher&amp;rsquo;s mouth behavior offline.
I wanna contain the spread of corona virus and I will care about infection seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-28: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Free talk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28-ts3-unit8-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-28-ts3-unit8-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Free talk: 8.What would you do? 1. If you had an hour to spare right now, what would you do? If I had an hour to spare right now, I would take a nap. Because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well last night. I wake up at 3 am in these days, I don&amp;rsquo;t have no idea. And I sometimes can&amp;rsquo;t sleep again.
2. If you had one month of free time, what would you do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-25: so irritated today</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-25/</guid>
      <description>I was so irritated today. Yesterday I presented what I&amp;rsquo;ve done in these days, but some my colleagues couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand that. So I was going to try to explain it in detail today.
It seems to me that they take for granted that I do research and told them gently what they can&amp;rsquo;t understand. They think the reason they don&amp;rsquo;t understand is because I don&amp;rsquo;t explain to them, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-22: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-22-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-22-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 2. Speaking and writing: What would you change? A. If you Had last year to live over again, what would you change? Think of answers to the questions, and make notes below. Is there &amp;hellip;
 a place you&amp;rsquo;d go more often?  I would go surfing more often. Last year, I didn&amp;rsquo;t go surfing so much. Because, I hurt right hip joint and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have warm wet suits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-19: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-19-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:16:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-19-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 1. Reading D. Discuss these questions 1. What have been the most important things in the writer&amp;rsquo;s life?  to be relaxed and live peacefully. to try new things and enjoy them. to be respected by others&amp;hellip;. his or her family and friends to spend time on something worth, like exciting experiences, visiting around the world like that. to enjoy life without worry.  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-15: Review and my last few days</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 19:09:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-15/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I and my teacher cleared my goals of learning English in Cebu.
My goals are, firstly, to speak general English smoothly, frequently, and naturally. Because I want to enjoy small talks with people who I meet in trip. If I could do that, I could have new idea and thought to enjoy my life through their culture, history, custom, and etc.
Secondary is to get a job abroad, like the United States, the United Kingdom, Singapore, Australia, or New Zealand, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-13-ts3-unit8-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-13-ts3-unit8-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.D: Any regrets? 1. Reading A. What kinds of things do people regret in life? Make a class list. I think&amp;hellip; Some people wish they had got married with another partner. Because some Japanese husband and wife are always complaining about their partner.
And, Someone who had a car accident wishes he had paid more attention, I think. Especially someone is still suffering from the aftereffects of the car accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-12: Review and my last few days</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 19:17:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-12/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned about how to use &amp;ldquo;that would be&amp;rdquo; for commenting on a suggestion or a possibility. And I practiced to ask about imaginary situations and answer the questions.
Furthermore, I learned about &amp;lsquo;neat&amp;rsquo; and &amp;ldquo;why not?&amp;rdquo;. You can use &amp;ldquo;that would be neat&amp;rdquo;, when you listen to someone who talked you about reasonable and simple idea to solve a problem. And you can use &amp;ldquo;why not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: That would be &amp;hellip;  If you could do something really different, what would you do?   I&amp;rsquo;d fly to the moon if I could. I want to walk on the moon once. It&amp;rsquo;s like bouncing on the trampoline, I guess. It must be fun.  If you could have any job, what would you do?   Marine biologist and fish farmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-09: Review and my last weekend</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned about advising using &amp;ldquo;if I were you&amp;rdquo;. And I practiced advising for people who have these worries.
I worked from home today as I did last week. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna work from home this week and work at office from next week, however I will work from home also next week, I guess. Because Corona virus haven&amp;rsquo;t been calmed down yet.
I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of world&amp;rsquo;s economic collapse rather than corona virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-05: WFM and 1on1 meeting</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:44:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-05/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home also today. I stared to work at 7:00am and finished at 3:30pm. Because I wanted to surf. There were good waves today. Actually, it was a little big wave, so I was swallowed up by the wave many times. However, I enjoyed very much.
And I talked my boss about this year&amp;rsquo;s result. I changed my department next to previous department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-04: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:45:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 1. Conversation strategy: Giving advice A. What tough decisions have you made? Did you ask for advice? Tell the class. I had made tough decision to go to which grad school. One of them was Osaka University where I got bachelor degree, Another one was NARA Institute of Science and Technology(NAIST).
Osaka University is in the urban city and you can go to center of Osaka city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-02: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:23:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of asking about imaginary situations or events. I answered the notebook&amp;rsquo;s questions and made a question using &amp;ldquo;what would do &amp;hellip;, if &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Furthermore, I learned words below.
 diabetes  a serious disease in which there is too much sugar in your blood   charge you for &amp;hellip;  to ask someone for particular amount of money for something your are selling   keep them  take them   waning  when the moon wanes, you gradually see less of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-02: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:14:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. It&amp;rsquo;s due to avoid infecting with corona virus, of course. Forty percents of employee in my office work from home. Rest of them have to work at the office because they should handle specific hardware there. And unfortunately, IT department in my office didn&amp;rsquo;t suppose that so many employees connect from home to the office at the same time so that it was hard to connect from home to the office network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-01: Surfing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-01/</guid>
      <description>I went surfing in the evening and then I had a dinner. I used to watch TV or movie after dinner. However I was exhausted due to surfing, so I went to bed soon. It was about at nine or ten.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I don&amp;rsquo;t sleep well after I was exhausted. I woke up at 3:00 am and couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep since then. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that I will be sleepy today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-28: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:26:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about dilemmas and some verbs + prepositions. Dilemma means a situation in which it&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to decide what to do, because all the choices seem equally good or equally bad. Longman dictionary says that. I answered questions which have dilemmas.
And today, I worked from home all day. It&amp;rsquo;s due to avoid infecting with corona virus. My company told all employees not to work at the office as possible as they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:38:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.B: Life&amp;rsquo;s little dilemmas 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. Listen and take the quiz. Circle your answers. Then compare with a partner.  b   It&amp;rsquo;s depends on the friend, I mean that it depends on the closeness with the friend. If the friend is one of my best friends, I never let the friend buy a new one. But unless the friend is my best friend, I would let the friend pay for it, definitely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 21:02:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of wishes and imaginary situations or events. And I made some sentences with wishes and imaginary situations. Furthermore, I started lesson B about dilemmas. I made some sentences which have dilemmas, however I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do well. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t feel dilemmas, I live simply every day, I guess.
Anyway, at the next lesson, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna continue to learn about dilemmas. My homework is to make some sentences about my dilemmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 3. Listening and speaking: Just one wish  He wishes he could just sit down and watch TV.   Because he needs to do laundry.  She wishes she went out more with her friends.   Because She can&amp;rsquo;t afford to go out more.  He wishes he could get together with his family more often.   Because He doesn&amp;rsquo;t live near his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: What is Zen?</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:29:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24/</guid>
      <description>At last lesson, my teacher Cathy said that I have to research about Zen and I have to tell her what is Zen and how to do Zen. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to explain about Zen, I think. Because Zen is one of religions, so it must be complicated and confusing. At first, I searched Zen by Google.
Zen is one of training of Zenshu. Zenshu is one sect of Buddhism, and the goal of Zenshu is to attain spiritual enlightenment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 1. Getting started A. What would you like more of in your life? I can&amp;rsquo;t speak English smoothly and naturally. So I wish I could speak English well. If I could speak English well, I could enjoy movies, musical, and trip more than before, definitely. Furthermore, if I do that, I&amp;rsquo;d get a interesting job and work happily. And if I win a lottery, I&amp;rsquo;d probably take long vacations to go all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: WFM</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 15:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-21/</guid>
      <description>I worked at home, today and last Wednesday. Because Corona virus is out-breaking now in Japan, so that I avoid crowed places as possible as I can.
Some people says it&amp;rsquo;s too much to worry about. Yeah, I know. But, my wife is weak, so it will be a problem if she is infected with corona virus. Because corona virus kills people who have a health problem.
I wish that corona virus doesn&amp;rsquo;t spread any more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-8</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Description about the pictures 1 There is an doctor and a nurse. They are in a hospital room. They smile with confidence, as I see it.
2. There is a rich house with a garden and a convertible car. A rich family live there, I guess.
3. There is an old man and an old lady, their children and grand children. It&amp;rsquo;s a celebration to mark the forty or fifty anniversary of their marriage, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 3. Writing: Your circle of friends A. Think about three of your friends. Tell a partner about them. Discuss the questions below.  What is your friend like? How did you meet? Why did you become friends? What do you have in common? What do you do together?  B. Read the article below and the Help note. Then write an article like the one page 66 about your circle of friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 2. Speaking and listening: Getting back in touch  His college friends   G: So what are you doing this weekend, Javier? J: Oh, I have to do something around my house.  You know, do the laundry, go food shopping, the kind of stuff. How about you?   G: Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go see the new science fiction movie that&amp;rsquo;s playing downtown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-12: A trip to Sapporo</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-12/</guid>
      <description>I went to Sapporo last weekend. It was the first time to visit Sapporo for me. I enjoyed a snowy landscape, Snow festival, and food and drink, of course. It was an amazing trip totally.
When I arrived at Chitose airport, it was not much cold. I felt it was the same temperature as Kanagawa. It was negative two degrees in Sapporo and positive two degrees in Kanagawa, actually. It was just a little bit difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-05: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:44:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 1. Reading A. What are some good ways to make new friends? Make a list.  Join new community, club or something.. Ask your friends to introduce someone to you. Do something new. Go some places where you have never been. Be friendly for strangers. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to talk to strangers. Talking with smile and laughing happily. Don&amp;rsquo;t complain or blame someone, I mean you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say negative things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.C: She&amp;rsquo;s just a bit odd. 1. Conversation strategy: Softening comments A. What are your neighbors like? Do you get along with them? Tell the class. My neighbors next door are a man and his daughter. It seems to me that they get along well, because I sometimes see they&amp;rsquo;re talking with smile. But late at night once or twice, I heard him to shout like being drunk, so I&amp;rsquo;m bit worried about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Before starting Lesson C. I will do homework about Lesson B.
Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B, Section.2 A.7-9 7. First dates usually turn out to be a disaster! I agree with that partially. Not usually, sometimes it turns out to be a disaster. Because someone who don&amp;rsquo;t know each other may not be able to have a nice chat at the first date. The person don&amp;rsquo;t know what the another person like and don&amp;rsquo;t like, so that sometimes the person do something what the another person don&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-25: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-25/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s I worked from home. I hate commuting, so I was able to be relaxed and work. I did some tutorials to make AWS Greengrass on Raspberry Pi connect to AWS. I had some troubles, but I made it.
I had wrist-ache. I don&amp;rsquo;t the reason, but I have been typed a keyboard too much, I think. It&amp;rsquo;s painful even if I do nothing. I hope that it&amp;rsquo;s cured soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B: Dating 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. High school sweethearts I have some questions about vocabularies.
&amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;work out&amp;rdquo; emphasizes this expression? If this statement doesn&amp;rsquo;t use &amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo;, does it have the same meanings?
What does &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; mean? I think that there is an inconsistency between &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo;. Because &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; means the current and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; means the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Today is a sleepy day.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20/</guid>
      <description>I have been really sleepy today. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well last night, because I did exercise too much for the first time in three weeks, I think.
Yesterday, I went jogging for an hour at the seaside, and I walked for two hours to play game, Dragon Quest walk, kind of Pokemon go. I was too tired so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have enough sleep.
The reason that I did too much exercise is the&amp;hellip; No special reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 18:17:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.A: Circle of friends 1. Getting started A. Where do people make friends? How many places can you think of? Make a list. I think people make friends at school, workplace, clubs, and introducing from friends.
 school an introduction from friends workplace sports club  B. Listen and read the article above. How did Christopher meet his friends? He met his friends at college and work, or through his friends, and near his home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-19: Weekend and a bad end</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-19/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was relaxing days. I went to the city library and borrowed a book, the title is &amp;ldquo;Talking to My Daughter About the Economy.&amp;rdquo;. I didn&amp;rsquo;t read it yet.
After that I went to shopping at near super market and bought lots of food and drink. Because I had a trip to Aomori two weekends ago, so that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go to shopping.
In addition, I run at the seaside for about 1 hour, 10 kilo meters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Checkpoint</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</guid>
      <description>4. What&amp;rsquo;s going to happen?  Cindy: What time does your train leave (leave)today? Dana: I &#39;m gonna take (take)the 3:30 train. Oh, no, it&amp;rsquo;s almost 3:00! Cindy: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry. I &#39;ll drive (drive)you to the station. Dana: Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to do that. I will call (call)a taxi. Cindy: No way! I can take you. I &#39;m gonna go (go)to the mall this afternoon. It&amp;rsquo;s not far from the train station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-14: Trip to Aomori for the first time</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-14/</guid>
      <description>I and my wife enjoyed a 3-days trip in Aomori last weekend. We traveled by train. I have never taken the Tohoku shinkansen until this time. I was looking forward to a train lunch box in the Tohoku shinkansen. Unfortunately, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t sold in the train. I don&amp;rsquo;t why it wasn&amp;rsquo;t, however, I was disappointed with that. Probably, Tokyo lunch box isn&amp;rsquo;t popular very much.
Day 1, after four and half hours train, we arrived in Aomori at 1:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-10: Review and my department transfer</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</guid>
      <description>At yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned to build sentences using common collocations with do, make, and etc. In addition, I reviewed unit 4 to 6 through some exercises. I could respond some questions quickly rather than before, relatively. I used too many times &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; as conjunctions, though. I will use vary conjunctions next lesson.
At last I&amp;rsquo;ll be transferred to new department. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna work in the Cloud development team. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to move a office, just 5 meters move in the same office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-08: Happy birthday</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-08/</guid>
      <description>Today is my wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday. I presented fluffy pajamas, champagne and a champagne glass to her. She was very pleased and I was glad to see that. The fluffy pajamas was Gelato pique&amp;rsquo;s one that she&amp;rsquo;s been wanted before. Champagne was Veuve Clicquot that is the one of her favorite. And the champagne glass was Riedel&amp;rsquo;s one. Riedel&amp;rsquo;s glass makes a difference in taste of wine.
Even if you aren&amp;rsquo;t a wine expert, you can feel the difference between normal glass and Riedel&amp;rsquo;s one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 2.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</guid>
      <description>D. Read the Help note. Then read the question and answer with as long as, provided that, or unless. Question I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more organized, so I decided to record my lectures, but I never have time to watch them. Any ideas?
Answer You can&amp;rsquo;t remember what you learned, unless you review your lectures. So, you ought to find time to review your lectures, however, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to watch the recordings - provided that you remember the key points of your lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-01: Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-01/</guid>
      <description>I welcomed the New Year while watching a comedy TV program. I feel that it&amp;rsquo;s very happy to greet the New Year while laughing.
Unfortunately, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t see the sunrise and Mt.Fuji on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day because of thick cloud. Today we ate Zouni as brunch. My wife cooked Hakata Zouni which is localized in Hakata region. It contains Mochi, Katsuona(a kind of leaf mustard), Buri(a yellowtail fish), and etc. It&amp;rsquo;s really tasty, I like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-31: New year&#39;s eve</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-31/</guid>
      <description>Today I and my wife ate Toshikoshi-soba for lunch. My wife cooked it for us. Eating toshikoshi-soba is the traditional custom in Japan. We Japanese wish healthful long life and eat it on new year&amp;rsquo;s eve. The long soba noodles symbolize a long life. The buckwheat plant can survive severe weather during growing period, so that soba represents strength and resiliency.
After lunch, I went surfing. There were fine waves and I enjoyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-30: Christmas presents from America</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-30/</guid>
      <description>I received Christmas presents from my brother who lives in Michigan, America. I love American foods, spices and snacks.
I went to America on my way of honeymoon. I wanted to introduce my wife to my brother&amp;rsquo;s family. And I&amp;rsquo;d like to eat American and Canadian foods, and see the Niagara falls again.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been there with my dad and mom three years ago. It was an amazing experience, but it was not enough to visit there only once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-28: A relaxing day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-28/</guid>
      <description>I was relaxed today totally. I watched some TV shows, that were recorded before, late last night. And I woke up about eleven o&amp;rsquo;clock. I and my wife had a lunch and went shopping to buy some food and drink for new year&amp;rsquo;s eve and new year&amp;rsquo;s days.
And I went surfing. There were comfortable waves and I could enjoy surfing.
That&amp;rsquo;s it. I wish I could have a day like today every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&amp;rsquo;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1. Reading A. Do you ever multitask? What kinds of things do you do at the same time? Is multitasking a good thing to do? About 20 years ago, when I was at network operation team in the previous company, I sometimes did multitask.
When I was in a network trouble, I&amp;rsquo;ve done multitask. It was calling customer, solving the problems, writing the report, asking my colleague to help me by a chat tool, and explaining that to my boss at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-12: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson C: I&amp;rsquo;ve got to get going. 1. Conversation strategy: Ending phone conversations A. When was the last time you were running late? Why? It was last Saturday, because I was going to be late for a appointment of the dental clinic. My appointment was 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock, but I woke up 9:35. The dental clinic is a 5 minutes away by bicycle. So, I had to get ready to go out in 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&amp;rsquo;ve got to learn those.
And I&amp;rsquo;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&amp;rsquo;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>