<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&#39;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&#39;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-16: A first ophthalmic clinic</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday, I went to a dental clinic, not for cleaning. It&#39;s for making mouthpiece. I sometimes grind my teeth while sleeping. It&#39;s for preventing from that. Cathy said that in Philippines we slap the person who grinds teeth in a sleep. Oh, my gosh. I won&#39;t tell that to my wife.
And I went to a ophthalmic clinic for the first time. I have never been to a ophthalmic clinic, because I have good eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1. Reading A. Do you ever multitask? What kinds of things do you do at the same time? Is multitasking a good thing to do? About 20 years ago, when I was at network operation team in the previous company, I sometimes did multitask.
When I was in a network trouble, I&#39;ve done multitask. It was calling customer, solving the problems, writing the report, asking my colleague to help me by a chat tool, and explaining that to my boss at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-12: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson C: I&#39;ve got to get going. 1. Conversation strategy: Ending phone conversations A. When was the last time you were running late? Why? It was last Saturday, because I was going to be late for a appointment of the dental clinic. My appointment was 10 o&#39;clock, but I woke up 9:35. The dental clinic is a 5 minutes away by bicycle. So, I had to get ready to go out in 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&#39;ve got to learn those.
And I&#39;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&#39;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>