<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in private life on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 19:17:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/private-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-12: Review and my last few days</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 19:17:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-12/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned about how to use &amp;ldquo;that would be&amp;rdquo; for commenting on a suggestion or a possibility. And I practiced to ask about imaginary situations and answer the questions.
Furthermore, I learned about &amp;lsquo;neat&amp;rsquo; and &amp;ldquo;why not?&amp;quot;. You can use &amp;ldquo;that would be neat&amp;rdquo;, when you listen to someone who talked you about reasonable and simple idea to solve a problem. And you can use &amp;ldquo;why not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 2. Strategy plus: That would be &amp;hellip;  If you could do something really different, what would you do?   I&amp;rsquo;d fly to the moon if I could. I want to walk on the moon once. It&amp;rsquo;s like bouncing on the trampoline, I guess. It must be fun.  If you could have any job, what would you do?   Marine biologist and fish farmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-09: Review and my last weekend</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-09/</guid>
      <description>At the last lesson, I learned about advising using &amp;ldquo;if I were you&amp;rdquo;. And I practiced advising for people who have these worries.
I worked from home today as I did last week. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna work from home this week and work at office from next week, however I will work from home also next week, I guess. Because Corona virus haven&amp;rsquo;t been calmed down yet.
I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of world&amp;rsquo;s economic collapse rather than corona virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-05: WFM and 1on1 meeting</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:44:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-05/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home also today. I stared to work at 7:00am and finished at 3:30pm. Because I wanted to surf. There were good waves today. Actually, it was a little big wave, so I was swallowed up by the wave many times. However, I enjoyed very much.
And I talked my boss about this year&amp;rsquo;s result. I changed my department next to previous department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-04: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:45:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-04-ts3-unit8-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.C: If I were you, &amp;hellip; 1. Conversation strategy: Giving advice A. What tough decisions have you made? Did you ask for advice? Tell the class. I had made tough decision to go to which grad school. One of them was Osaka University where I got bachelor degree, Another one was NARA Institute of Science and Technology(NAIST).
Osaka University is in the urban city and you can go to center of Osaka city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-02: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:23:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of asking about imaginary situations or events. I answered the notebook&amp;rsquo;s questions and made a question using &amp;ldquo;what would do &amp;hellip;, if &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Furthermore, I learned words below.
 diabetes  a serious disease in which there is too much sugar in your blood   charge you for &amp;hellip;  to ask someone for particular amount of money for something your are selling   keep them  take them   waning  when the moon wanes, you gradually see less of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-02: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:14:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-02/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. It&amp;rsquo;s due to avoid infecting with corona virus, of course. Forty percents of employee in my office work from home. Rest of them have to work at the office because they should handle specific hardware there. And unfortunately, IT department in my office didn&amp;rsquo;t suppose that so many employees connect from home to the office at the same time so that it was hard to connect from home to the office network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-03-01: Surfing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-03-01/</guid>
      <description>I went surfing in the evening and then I had a dinner. I used to watch TV or movie after dinner. However I was exhausted due to surfing, so I went to bed soon. It was about at nine or ten.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I don&amp;rsquo;t sleep well after I was exhausted. I woke up at 3:00 am and couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep since then. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that I will be sleepy today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-28: Review the last lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:26:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-28/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about dilemmas and some verbs + prepositions. Dilemma means a situation in which it&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to decide what to do, because all the choices seem equally good or equally bad. Longman dictionary says that. I answered questions which have dilemmas.
And today, I worked from home all day. It&amp;rsquo;s due to avoid infecting with corona virus. My company told all employees not to work at the office as possible as they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:38:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.B: Life&amp;rsquo;s little dilemmas 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. Listen and take the quiz. Circle your answers. Then compare with a partner.  b   It&amp;rsquo;s depends on the friend, I mean that it depends on the closeness with the friend. If the friend is one of my best friends, I never let the friend buy a new one. But unless the friend is my best friend, I would let the friend pay for it, definitely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 21:02:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-review/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about grammar of wishes and imaginary situations or events. And I made some sentences with wishes and imaginary situations. Furthermore, I started lesson B about dilemmas. I made some sentences which have dilemmas, however I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do well. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t feel dilemmas, I live simply every day, I guess.
Anyway, at the next lesson, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna continue to learn about dilemmas. My homework is to make some sentences about my dilemmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 3. Listening and speaking: Just one wish  He wishes he could just sit down and watch TV.   Because he needs to do laundry.  She wishes she went out more with her friends.   Because She can&amp;rsquo;t afford to go out more.  He wishes he could get together with his family more often.   Because He doesn&amp;rsquo;t live near his family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-24: What is Zen?</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:29:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-24/</guid>
      <description>At last lesson, my teacher Cathy said that I have to research about Zen and I have to tell her what is Zen and how to do Zen. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to explain about Zen, I think. Because Zen is one of religions, so it must be complicated and confusing. At first, I searched Zen by Google.
Zen is one of training of Zenshu. Zenshu is one sect of Buddhism, and the goal of Zenshu is to attain spiritual enlightenment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 1. Getting started A. What would you like more of in your life? I can&amp;rsquo;t speak English smoothly and naturally. So I wish I could speak English well. If I could speak English well, I could enjoy movies, musical, and trip more than before, definitely. Furthermore, if I do that, I&amp;rsquo;d get a interesting job and work happily. And if I win a lottery, I&amp;rsquo;d probably take long vacations to go all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: WFM</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 15:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-21/</guid>
      <description>I worked at home, today and last Wednesday. Because Corona virus is out-breaking now in Japan, so that I avoid crowed places as possible as I can.
Some people says it&amp;rsquo;s too much to worry about. Yeah, I know. But, my wife is weak, so it will be a problem if she is infected with corona virus. Because corona virus kills people who have a health problem.
I wish that corona virus doesn&amp;rsquo;t spread any more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-8</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Description about the pictures 1 There is an doctor and a nurse. They are in a hospital room. They smile with confidence, as I see it.
2. There is a rich house with a garden and a convertible car. A rich family live there, I guess.
3. There is an old man and an old lady, their children and grand children. It&amp;rsquo;s a celebration to mark the forty or fifty anniversary of their marriage, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 3. Writing: Your circle of friends A. Think about three of your friends. Tell a partner about them. Discuss the questions below.  What is your friend like? How did you meet? Why did you become friends? What do you have in common? What do you do together?  B. Read the article below and the Help note. Then write an article like the one page 66 about your circle of friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 2. Speaking and listening: Getting back in touch  His college friends   G: So what are you doing this weekend, Javier? J: Oh, I have to do something around my house.  You know, do the laundry, go food shopping, the kind of stuff. How about you?   G: Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go see the new science fiction movie that&amp;rsquo;s playing downtown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-12: A trip to Sapporo</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-12/</guid>
      <description>I went to Sapporo last weekend. It was the first time to visit Sapporo for me. I enjoyed a snowy landscape, Snow festival, and food and drink, of course. It was an amazing trip totally.
When I arrived at Chitose airport, it was not much cold. I felt it was the same temperature as Kanagawa. It was negative two degrees in Sapporo and positive two degrees in Kanagawa, actually. It was just a little bit difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-05: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:44:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 1. Reading A. What are some good ways to make new friends? Make a list.  Join new community, club or something.. Ask your friends to introduce someone to you. Do something new. Go some places where you have never been. Be friendly for strangers. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to talk to strangers. Talking with smile and laughing happily. Don&amp;rsquo;t complain or blame someone, I mean you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say negative things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.C: She&amp;rsquo;s just a bit odd. 1. Conversation strategy: Softening comments A. What are your neighbors like? Do you get along with them? Tell the class. My neighbors next door are a man and his daughter. It seems to me that they get along well, because I sometimes see they&amp;rsquo;re talking with smile. But late at night once or twice, I heard him to shout like being drunk, so I&amp;rsquo;m bit worried about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Before starting Lesson C. I will do homework about Lesson B.
Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B, Section.2 A.7-9 7. First dates usually turn out to be a disaster! I agree with that partially. Not usually, sometimes it turns out to be a disaster. Because someone who don&amp;rsquo;t know each other may not be able to have a nice chat at the first date. The person don&amp;rsquo;t know what the another person like and don&amp;rsquo;t like, so that sometimes the person do something what the another person don&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-25: WFH</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-25/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s I worked from home. I hate commuting, so I was able to be relaxed and work. I did some tutorials to make AWS Greengrass on Raspberry Pi connect to AWS. I had some troubles, but I made it.
I had wrist-ache. I don&amp;rsquo;t the reason, but I have been typed a keyboard too much, I think. It&amp;rsquo;s painful even if I do nothing. I hope that it&amp;rsquo;s cured soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B: Dating 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. High school sweethearts I have some questions about vocabularies.
&amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;work out&amp;rdquo; emphasizes this expression? If this statement doesn&amp;rsquo;t use &amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo;, does it have the same meanings?
What does &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; mean? I think that there is an inconsistency between &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo;. Because &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; means the current and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; means the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Today is a sleepy day.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20/</guid>
      <description>I have been really sleepy today. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well last night, because I did exercise too much for the first time in three weeks, I think.
Yesterday, I went jogging for an hour at the seaside, and I walked for two hours to play game, Dragon Quest walk, kind of Pokemon go. I was too tired so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have enough sleep.
The reason that I did too much exercise is the&amp;hellip; No special reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 18:17:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.A: Circle of friends 1. Getting started A. Where do people make friends? How many places can you think of? Make a list. I think people make friends at school, workplace, clubs, and introducing from friends.
 school an introduction from friends workplace sports club  B. Listen and read the article above. How did Christopher meet his friends? He met his friends at college and work, or through his friends, and near his home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-19: Weekend and a bad end</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-19/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was relaxing days. I went to the city library and borrowed a book, the title is &amp;ldquo;Talking to My Daughter About the Economy.&amp;quot;. I didn&amp;rsquo;t read it yet.
After that I went to shopping at near super market and bought lots of food and drink. Because I had a trip to Aomori two weekends ago, so that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go to shopping.
In addition, I run at the seaside for about 1 hour, 10 kilo meters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Checkpoint</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</guid>
      <description>4. What&amp;rsquo;s going to happen?  Cindy: What time does your train leave (leave)today? Dana: I &#39;m gonna take (take)the 3:30 train. Oh, no, it&amp;rsquo;s almost 3:00! Cindy: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry. I &#39;ll drive (drive)you to the station. Dana: Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to do that. I will call (call)a taxi. Cindy: No way! I can take you. I &#39;m gonna go (go)to the mall this afternoon. It&amp;rsquo;s not far from the train station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-14: Trip to Aomori for the first time</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-14/</guid>
      <description>I and my wife enjoyed a 3-days trip in Aomori last weekend. We traveled by train. I have never taken the Tohoku shinkansen until this time. I was looking forward to a train lunch box in the Tohoku shinkansen. Unfortunately, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t sold in the train. I don&amp;rsquo;t why it wasn&amp;rsquo;t, however, I was disappointed with that. Probably, Tokyo lunch box isn&amp;rsquo;t popular very much.
Day 1, after four and half hours train, we arrived in Aomori at 1:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-10: Review and my department transfer</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-10/</guid>
      <description>At yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned to build sentences using common collocations with do, make, and etc. In addition, I reviewed unit 4 to 6 through some exercises. I could respond some questions quickly rather than before, relatively. I used too many times &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; as conjunctions, though. I will use vary conjunctions next lesson.
At last I&amp;rsquo;ll be transferred to new department. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna work in the Cloud development team. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to move a office, just 5 meters move in the same office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-08: Happy birthday</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-08/</guid>
      <description>Today is my wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday. I presented fluffy pajamas, champagne and a champagne glass to her. She was very pleased and I was glad to see that. The fluffy pajamas was Gelato pique&amp;rsquo;s one that she&amp;rsquo;s been wanted before. Champagne was Veuve Clicquot that is the one of her favorite. And the champagne glass was Riedel&amp;rsquo;s one. Riedel&amp;rsquo;s glass makes a difference in taste of wine.
Even if you aren&amp;rsquo;t a wine expert, you can feel the difference between normal glass and Riedel&amp;rsquo;s one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 2.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</guid>
      <description>D. Read the Help note. Then read the question and answer with as long as, provided that, or unless. Question I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more organized, so I decided to record my lectures, but I never have time to watch them. Any ideas?
Answer You can&amp;rsquo;t remember what you learned, unless you review your lectures. So, you ought to find time to review your lectures, however, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to watch the recordings - provided that you remember the key points of your lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-01: Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-01/</guid>
      <description>I welcomed the New Year while watching a comedy TV program. I feel that it&amp;rsquo;s very happy to greet the New Year while laughing.
Unfortunately, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t see the sunrise and Mt.Fuji on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day because of thick cloud. Today we ate Zouni as brunch. My wife cooked Hakata Zouni which is localized in Hakata region. It contains Mochi, Katsuona(a kind of leaf mustard), Buri(a yellowtail fish), and etc. It&amp;rsquo;s really tasty, I like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-31: New year&#39;s eve</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-31/</guid>
      <description>Today I and my wife ate Toshikoshi-soba for lunch. My wife cooked it for us. Eating toshikoshi-soba is the traditional custom in Japan. We Japanese wish healthful long life and eat it on new year&amp;rsquo;s eve. The long soba noodles symbolize a long life. The buckwheat plant can survive severe weather during growing period, so that soba represents strength and resiliency.
After lunch, I went surfing. There were fine waves and I enjoyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-30: Christmas presents from America</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-30/</guid>
      <description>I received Christmas presents from my brother who lives in Michigan, America. I love American foods, spices and snacks.
I went to America on my way of honeymoon. I wanted to introduce my wife to my brother&amp;rsquo;s family. And I&amp;rsquo;d like to eat American and Canadian foods, and see the Niagara falls again.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been there with my dad and mom three years ago. It was an amazing experience, but it was not enough to visit there only once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-28: A relaxing day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-28/</guid>
      <description>I was relaxed today totally. I watched some TV shows, that were recorded before, late last night. And I woke up about eleven o&amp;rsquo;clock. I and my wife had a lunch and went shopping to buy some food and drink for new year&amp;rsquo;s eve and new year&amp;rsquo;s days.
And I went surfing. There were comfortable waves and I could enjoy surfing.
That&amp;rsquo;s it. I wish I could have a day like today every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&amp;rsquo;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1. Reading A. Do you ever multitask? What kinds of things do you do at the same time? Is multitasking a good thing to do? About 20 years ago, when I was at network operation team in the previous company, I sometimes did multitask.
When I was in a network trouble, I&amp;rsquo;ve done multitask. It was calling customer, solving the problems, writing the report, asking my colleague to help me by a chat tool, and explaining that to my boss at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-12: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-12-ts3-unit6-c/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson C: I&amp;rsquo;ve got to get going. 1. Conversation strategy: Ending phone conversations A. When was the last time you were running late? Why? It was last Saturday, because I was going to be late for a appointment of the dental clinic. My appointment was 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock, but I woke up 9:35. The dental clinic is a 5 minutes away by bicycle. So, I had to get ready to go out in 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&amp;rsquo;ve got to learn those.
And I&amp;rsquo;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&amp;rsquo;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>