<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>public life on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/public-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in public life on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 10:10:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/public-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-07-22: Touchstone-3 Unit-12</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-07-22-ts3-unit12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 10:10:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-07-22-ts3-unit12/</guid>
      <description>Unit-12: In the news I describe pictures in the textbook.
 A newscaster is explaining some news happened today. A person is going to sing up for twitter. Several newspaper is sold in the news stand. A person is reading world news using a tablet computer.  Before you begin &amp;hellip;  How do you find out about what&amp;rsquo;s going on in the world?  I read news on websites almost everyday, sometimes watch news programmes on TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-28: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28-ts3-unit10-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:35:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-28-ts3-unit10-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.D: Reviews 1. Reading A. Do you ever read reviews before deciding to see a movie? Are the reviews usually accurate? Tell the class. I&amp;rsquo;ve read reviews before deciding to see a movie. However, The reviews aren&amp;rsquo;t usually accurate for me, they&amp;rsquo;re rather too much praise for the movie. So, I usually avoid reading any reviews before watching a movie.
B. Read the movie review and the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-25: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-25-ts3-unit10-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 18:54:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-25-ts3-unit10-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.C: I was wondering &amp;hellip; 3. Listening and strategies: Favors at work 1. Peter  P: Um, Excuse me. Do you have a minute? B: Sure, Um. Hold on, Peter. Let me just finish this email. B: All right. What can I do for you? P: Well. Do you know the report you ask me to do for tomorrow? B: Yes. P: Well, Um. I was wondering if I could have a little more time to work on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-10 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-21-ts3-unit10-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:30:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-21-ts3-unit10-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-10: What&amp;rsquo;s up? Lesson.C: I was wondering &amp;hellip; A. What kinds of favors might you ask a teacher for? I have asked my teacher to extend the deadline.
B. What favor does Jake ask his professor? Does his professor agree? Jake asks his professor for writing a reference by next Monday, because he&amp;rsquo;s been applying for jobs.
His professor agree with that, as long as Jake brings the information his professor needs at late afternoon tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-04-22: Japan rockdown can&#39;t be done</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:18:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-04-22/</guid>
      <description>Due to COVID-19, every countries&amp;rsquo; government have started lockdown. On the other hand, Japan government hasn&amp;rsquo;t started lockdown. Why?
The reason is that Japanese constitution don&amp;rsquo;t have the Act, like Emergency Powers Act in U.K or National Emergency Act in U.S.A. So, Japan rockdown can&amp;rsquo;t be done. The Act has power to restrict private rights for moving, shopping, business activities, like that. It&amp;rsquo;s useful for helping people under severe situations like terrible earthquakes, hurricanes or disease like this COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-04: Touchstone-2 Unit-1 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-04-ts2-unit1-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-04-ts2-unit1-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-1: Making friends Lesson.A: Getting to know you How well do you know your new classmates? YOUR NAME  What&amp;rsquo;s your name?   I&amp;rsquo;m Naoki Morita.  What does your name mean?   My name means Straight and Big-tree. My parents wished me to be honest, be confident, be gentle, and to value relationships with others.  Are you named after someone?   No, it&amp;rsquo;s not. My name was from my parents&amp;rsquo; wish, not named after anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-20: The first task in the new team</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Today, I worked for the Cloud development team for the first time. The task what I did was connecting PlayStation 4 controller with Raspberry Pi 4 Model B, and confirm the buttons which you pressed on the controller. It was so easy, but I was pleased with helping them.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got to make up my mind what I should do in the Cloud development team. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about building the development and operating environment of Machine-Learning with AWS and Jetson Nano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-19: TS3 Unit6 FreeTalk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s homework. At the last lesson, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk smoothly about the community event. So that It&amp;rsquo;s my homework.
Who&amp;rsquo;s going to do what? 1. When is the event going to be? Where? What time? We&amp;rsquo;d better hold the event during summer vacation. Because adults can take day-off easily.
We might want to hold the event from 5pm to 8pm. Because children had better sleep early, not staying up late at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-17: My new task</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-17/</guid>
      <description>I had a meeting about my new task yesterday. We talked about my wish, my skills and a new task of a Cloud Development team. We decided that I join the Cloud Development team temporary. For a while, I&amp;rsquo;ll work at the team and we&amp;rsquo;ll decide that I join the team officially.
I felt that the boss of the team is nice guy and the team members too, it&amp;rsquo;s a good team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&amp;rsquo;ve got to learn those.
And I&amp;rsquo;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&amp;rsquo;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>