<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>public life on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/public-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in public life on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 18:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/public-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-20: The first task in the new team</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Today, I worked for the Cloud development team for the first time. The task what I did was connecting PlayStation 4 controller with Raspberry Pi 4 Model B, and confirm the buttons which you pressed on the controller. It was so easy, but I was pleased with helping them.
I&#39;ve got to make up my mind what I should do in the Cloud development team. I&#39;m thinking about building the development and operating environment of Machine-Learning with AWS and Jetson Nano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-19: TS3 Unit6 FreeTalk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Today&#39;s homework. At the last lesson, I couldn&#39;t talk smoothly about the community event. So that It&#39;s my homework.
Who&#39;s going to do what? 1. When is the event going to be? Where? What time? We&#39;d better hold the event during summer vacation. Because adults can take day-off easily.
We might want to hold the event from 5pm to 8pm. Because children had better sleep early, not staying up late at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-17: My new task</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-17/</guid>
      <description>I had a meeting about my new task yesterday. We talked about my wish, my skills and a new task of a Cloud Development team. We decided that I join the Cloud Development team temporary. For a while, I&#39;ll work at the team and we&#39;ll decide that I join the team officially.
I felt that the boss of the team is nice guy and the team members too, it&#39;s a good team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-10: Review yesterday&#39;s lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>At the yesterday&#39;s lesson, I learned about reduction of verbs. Native speakers usually use reduction verbs, so that I&#39;ve got to learn those.
And I&#39;ll try to categorize vocabularies into each situations, because I can find proper words which express my feeling and thinking. If you categorize vocabularies into each situations in advance, you can find and choose your word easily.
At first I&#39;ll categorized vocabularies into 6 situations like common vocabulary, people, private life, public life, environment and nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>