<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>preparation on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/preparation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in preparation on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/preparation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-21: Touchstone-3 Unit-8 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Lesson.A: Wishes 1. Getting started A. What would you like more of in your life? I can&amp;rsquo;t speak English smoothly and naturally. So I wish I could speak English well. If I could speak English well, I could enjoy movies, musical, and trip more than before, definitely. Furthermore, if I do that, I&amp;rsquo;d get a interesting job and work happily. And if I win a lottery, I&amp;rsquo;d probably take long vacations to go all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-18: Touchstone-3 Unit-8</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 08:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-18-ts3-unit8/</guid>
      <description>Unit-8: What if? Description about the pictures 1 There is an doctor and a nurse. They are in a hospital room. They smile with confidence, as I see it.
2. There is a rich house with a garden and a convertible car. A rich family live there, I guess.
3. There is an old man and an old lady, their children and grand children. It&amp;rsquo;s a celebration to mark the forty or fifty anniversary of their marriage, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-17: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-17-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 3. Writing: Your circle of friends A. Think about three of your friends. Tell a partner about them. Discuss the questions below.  What is your friend like? How did you meet? Why did you become friends? What do you have in common? What do you do together?  B. Read the article below and the Help note. Then write an article like the one page 66 about your circle of friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-13-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 2. Speaking and listening: Getting back in touch  His college friends   G: So what are you doing this weekend, Javier? J: Oh, I have to do something around my house.  You know, do the laundry, go food shopping, the kind of stuff. How about you?   G: Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go see the new science fiction movie that&amp;rsquo;s playing downtown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-02-05: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:44:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-02-05-ts3-unit7-d/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.D: New friends, old friends 1. Reading A. What are some good ways to make new friends? Make a list.  Join new community, club or something.. Ask your friends to introduce someone to you. Do something new. Go some places where you have never been. Be friendly for strangers. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to talk to strangers. Talking with smile and laughing happily. Don&amp;rsquo;t complain or blame someone, I mean you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say negative things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-31: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.C</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-31-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.C: She&amp;rsquo;s just a bit odd. 1. Conversation strategy: Softening comments A. What are your neighbors like? Do you get along with them? Tell the class. My neighbors next door are a man and his daughter. It seems to me that they get along well, because I sometimes see they&amp;rsquo;re talking with smile. But late at night once or twice, I heard him to shout like being drunk, so I&amp;rsquo;m bit worried about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-27-ts3-unit7-c/</guid>
      <description>Before starting Lesson C. I will do homework about Lesson B.
Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B, Section.2 A.7-9 7. First dates usually turn out to be a disaster! I agree with that partially. Not usually, sometimes it turns out to be a disaster. Because someone who don&amp;rsquo;t know each other may not be able to have a nice chat at the first date. The person don&amp;rsquo;t know what the another person like and don&amp;rsquo;t like, so that sometimes the person do something what the another person don&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.B</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-23-ts3-unit7-b/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.B: Dating 1. Building vocabulary and grammar A. High school sweethearts I have some questions about vocabularies.
&amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;work out&amp;rdquo; emphasizes this expression? If this statement doesn&amp;rsquo;t use &amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo;, does it have the same meanings?
What does &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; mean? I think that there is an inconsistency between &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo;. Because &amp;ldquo;they are now living&amp;rdquo; means the current and &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; means the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-20: Touchstone-3 Unit-7 Lesson.A</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 18:17:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-20-ts3-unit7-a/</guid>
      <description>Unit-7: Relationships Lesson.A: Circle of friends 1. Getting started A. Where do people make friends? How many places can you think of? Make a list. I think people make friends at school, workplace, clubs, and introducing from friends.
 school an introduction from friends workplace sports club  B. Listen and read the article above. How did Christopher meet his friends? He met his friends at college and work, or through his friends, and near his home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Checkpoint</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-16-ts3-unit6-checkpoint/</guid>
      <description>4. What&amp;rsquo;s going to happen?  Cindy: What time does your train leave (leave)today? Dana: I &#39;m gonna take (take)the 3:30 train. Oh, no, it&amp;rsquo;s almost 3:00! Cindy: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry. I &#39;ll drive (drive)you to the station. Dana: Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to do that. I will call (call)a taxi. Cindy: No way! I can take you. I &#39;m gonna go (go)to the mall this afternoon. It&amp;rsquo;s not far from the train station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-09: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 page.62</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-09-ts3-unit6-p62/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-09-ts3-unit6-p62/</guid>
      <description>Vocabulary notebook 2. Write sentences to help you remember these expressions. Do some thinking I&amp;rsquo;m doing some thinking. But I have no idea.
Do something fun I want to do something fun. But I can&amp;rsquo;t make up my mind to do surfing, camping, or traveling.
Do volunteer work I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do volunteer work now. Because I&amp;rsquo;m really busy for work.
Make a decision I made a decision that affected my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-01-06: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 2.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-01-06-ts3-unit6-d-2d-p61/</guid>
      <description>D. Read the Help note. Then read the question and answer with as long as, provided that, or unless. Question I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more organized, so I decided to record my lectures, but I never have time to watch them. Any ideas?
Answer You can&amp;rsquo;t remember what you learned, unless you review your lectures. So, you ought to find time to review your lectures, however, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to watch the recordings - provided that you remember the key points of your lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&amp;rsquo;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-19: TS3 Unit6 FreeTalk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s homework. At the last lesson, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk smoothly about the community event. So that It&amp;rsquo;s my homework.
Who&amp;rsquo;s going to do what? 1. When is the event going to be? Where? What time? We&amp;rsquo;d better hold the event during summer vacation. Because adults can take day-off easily.
We might want to hold the event from 5pm to 8pm. Because children had better sleep early, not staying up late at night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>