<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>preparation on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/preparation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in preparation on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/preparation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-27: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D 1.C page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-27-ts3-unit6-d-1c-p61/</guid>
      <description>1.C. Deliver your experience and ask your partner about her experience using the phrases. 1. &amp;ldquo;play a trick on&amp;rdquo; original question: Have you played a trick on someone? How did it turn out?
I don&#39;t remember the last time when I played a trick on someone. Well, when I was a child, I and my friends were going back home from elementary school.
I caught a small frog and put it on the shoulder of my friend without being noticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-23: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D page.61</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-23-ts3-unit6-d-p61/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1.C. Replace the underlined words in each question with the correct form of an expression from the blog. Then ask and answer the questions with a partner.  Have you ever done something to fool played a trick onsomeone? How did it turn out? What do you do if you&#39;re not moving forward on making progress onan assignment. Do you often have your attention interrupted by get distracted byemail or phone calls?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-19: TS3 Unit6 FreeTalk</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-19-ts3-unit6-freetalk/</guid>
      <description>Today&#39;s homework. At the last lesson, I couldn&#39;t talk smoothly about the community event. So that It&#39;s my homework.
Who&#39;s going to do what? 1. When is the event going to be? Where? What time? We&#39;d better hold the event during summer vacation. Because adults can take day-off easily.
We might want to hold the event from 5pm to 8pm. Because children had better sleep early, not staying up late at night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>