<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>english on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in english on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2019-07-03: Time flies in English lessons</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-07-03/</guid>
      <description>I had an English lesson today. I feel I&amp;rsquo;ve not improve English skill very much. Maybe I have to study English harder everyday.. I should do my best effort to learn English, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t I ?
 The followings is my homework.
Describe 5 celebrities, share their personality and habits.  Kuro-chan, who is a comedian, is incredibly dishonest. He is always lying. Matchan, of the comedy duo &amp;ldquo;Downtown&amp;rdquo;, is extremely funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-27: It&#39;s a tiresome rainy day.</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-27/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s still raining today, however I forgot to bring my umbrella. Oh my gosh&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s, however, just drizzling rain.
 The followings will be my homework by tomorrow.
Unit 2. Experiences (page.11) Think of some special experiences you hope to have in the future. Tell the class&amp;hellip;
a place you&amp;rsquo;d like to go someday. I have many places I&amp;rsquo;d like to go. One of those is Iceland.
something you&amp;rsquo;d love to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-26: The usual day</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-26/</guid>
      <description>I got an English lesson today. I had a quiz that you make one word by choosing two memos from the ones with one word.
 back pack butter fly light house blue berry etc.  I thought it&amp;rsquo;s easy, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find some words. I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough vocabulary.
 The followings will be my homework by next Friday.
page.10: Vocabulary notebook 1. Rewrite the sentences so that they have an opposite meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-24: It&#39;s raining today again</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-24/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s raining today again.
Last night, May beetle was sticking to my cloth that was hanging out.
Summer is coming.
 The followings is my homework by next Wednesday.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t hear some of what they said. I should ask my teacher about them.
page.9: Lesson-D 2.Listening Listen to five people talk about themselves. Match the people and the things they will probably say next.
1. Ana I started lessons when I was in elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-21: work from home</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-21/</guid>
      <description>I worked from home today. Working from home is a lot easier as I don&amp;rsquo;t have to commute. Because it takes 1 hour and half to commute.
And more, there is no toilet problem. In Office, after lunch, almost toilets are always full. Reforming working style should be started from the toilet.
 And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have a English lesson this evening. The following is today&amp;rsquo;s homework.
Page.8: Lesson-D 1:Reading A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-19: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-19/</guid>
      <description>The following is homework I have to do by this evening.
 Page.7: Lesson-C 3.Strategies -Funny little habits- C. Talk about people with habits like these. Think of something positive to say. texting  My friend is always texting, even during talking. But at least his tweets are interesting.  chewing gum  Some people is always chewing gum, event at a formal event. But at least chewing gum calms their mind down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-18: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-18/</guid>
      <description>The following is homework I have to do by tomorrow.
Page.6: Lesson-C 1.D Change the underlined parts of these sentences to describe habits. Use always and a continuous verb.
 I&amp;rsquo;m pretty disorganized. I losethings.
I&amp;rsquo;m always losing things. Everyone in my family loves music. We singtogether.
We&amp;rsquo;re always singing together. My brother is really generous with his time. He fixesmy computer.
He&amp;rsquo;s always fixing my computer. My father is a workaholic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-06: TOUCHSTONE Student&#39;s Book 3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-06/</guid>
      <description>I use a textbook &amp;ldquo;TOUCHSTONE 2nd edition Student&amp;rsquo;s Book Level 3&amp;rdquo; in my English lesson. It&amp;rsquo;s at the low intermediate CFER level (A2-B1).
The followings are the homework I have to do by tomorrow.
page.5: Lesson-B 3.C Who do you admire ? I admire my brother.
Why ? Because, he works as a engineer in America. I also want to work as a engineer in America or Europe. I envy him working abroad and I&amp;rsquo;m proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-05: The English Lesson</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-05/</guid>
      <description>I took an English conversation lesson, it&amp;rsquo;s the first time I came back from my honeymoon.
I have visited England, Scotland, Canada and America in my honeymoon, so I thought that my English skill improve a little bit maybe, but it&amp;rsquo;s not at all.
I will study English harder than before so I can work abroad. Of course, I want to enjoy studying English. The proverb says, &amp;ldquo;what one likes, one will do well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
