<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summarize on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/summarize/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summarize on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/summarize/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2019-12-13: Touchstone-3 Unit-6 Lesson.D</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-12-13-ts3-unit6-d/</guid>
      <description>Touchstone-3 Unit-6: Managing life Lesson D: Less is more 1. Reading A. Do you ever multitask? What kinds of things do you do at the same time? Is multitasking a good thing to do? About 20 years ago, when I was at network operation team in the previous company, I sometimes did multitask.
When I was in a network trouble, I&amp;rsquo;ve done multitask. It was calling customer, solving the problems, writing the report, asking my colleague to help me by a chat tool, and explaining that to my boss at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-10-10: How to summarize an article</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:24:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Points  Rephrase the words and expressions used in the article to your own words and expressions Don&amp;rsquo;t mistake the conclusion Don&amp;rsquo;t claim your own idea   the author points out &amp;hellip; the author feels &amp;hellip;  Ignore examples sentences and modifiers  Procedure  Read whole the article at first   Distinguish between story trunks and branches  Write out the most important claims   They should be at the beginning and end  Write out an important statement of each paragraphs Rephrase them to your own words and expressions   Use &amp;quot;&amp;quot; when quoting a sentence  Summary of Barbara&amp;rsquo;s Blog  Overview   About taking meals with the family The author feels that families have little time together at mealtimes these days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
