<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:10:54 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-31: AWS DeepRacer League Workshop</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:10:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</guid>
      <description>AWS DeepRace League - Technical Workdshop Yesterday, I joined the &amp;ldquo;AWS Deep Racer League - Technical Workhop&amp;rdquo;, because I wanted to have fun learning about machine learning. The AWS DeepRacer is a 1&amp;frasl;18 scale racing car and it makes it possible to learn Reinforcement Learning (RL) in a fun way. It was disappointing that the hands-on was disabled due to a failure of the AWS service.
The presenter explained DeepRacer&amp;rsquo;s Reinforcement Learning and its simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-30: Surfed for the first time in two years</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 08:17:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I surfed for the first time in two years. The waves were waist high and very good for me. The water temperature was still a little cold and I needed a wetsuit.
Surfing after a long time was very pleasant and fun, I felt like going to keep surfing from now on.
This is the surfboard I used. It&amp;rsquo;s the Softech&amp;rsquo;s soft-surfboard: SALLY FITZGIBBONS SIGNATURE 7&amp;rsquo;0&amp;rdquo;. This long, buoyant surfboard is good for me because I am not strong and underexercised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-29: A TED talk that impressed me</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 07:48:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-29/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to build your confidence - and spark it others&amp;rdquo; I lose my confidence when I fail and disappointed myself,
when I was given cold stares, when I was blamed, and
when I was ignored.
This TED talk, Ms. Brittany Packnett&amp;rsquo;s speech, gives me a confidence.
It tells me that I need not lose my confidence.
Impressed words  Confidence is the necessary spark before everything that follows. Permission births confidence, community nurtures it and curiosity affirms it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>