<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vocabulary on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/vocabulary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vocabulary on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 18:05:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/vocabulary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-13: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-13-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 18:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-13-news/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about change of way of thinking about my life.
 Japan&amp;rsquo;s formula for life satisfaction  Ikigai means what it’s something you live for.
So far, or even now Japanese traditional companies valued not only company loyalty but input factors such as time and effort rather than output factors like results or progress. Long hours and sacrificed leisure time were (and still are) seen as positive virtues, while the “ganbaru” trait – meaning “trying hard” – is valued above all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-09: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-09-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 15:59:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-09-news/</guid>
      <description>Climate change: Could the coronavirus crisis spur a green recovery? I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about Ms. Greta Thunberg, a environment activist, reading the article below.
 Climate change: Could the coronavirus crisis spur a green recovery?  The drop in traffic due to corona virus is a major contributor to the fall in planet-warming CO2 emissions we&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed globally. Most people think climate change is as serious as coronavirus.
So, people will try to avoid using public transport system for fear of infection, and a plan of building road will be quit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-05-08: News</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-08-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-05-08-news/</guid>
      <description>I read some articles below.
Where&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s spirit of tolerance came from I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about characteristics of city culture, reading the article below.
 Where&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s spirit of tolerance came from  San Francisco has always been known as a city of nonconformity. But in recent decades, already-outlandish San Francisco rents and everyday prices has been inflating and living costs has been pushed to 25% higher than the national average.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>