<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>honeymoon on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/honeymoon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in honeymoon on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/honeymoon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-18: Honeymoon Day3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-18/</guid>
      <description>English Breakfast I ate English breakfast in England for the first time. It was lovely delicious.
Afternoon tea At last I had an afternoon tea in England. The tea is lovely tasty, and scones with plenty of clotted cream too. I enjoyed the afternoon tea.
Timeline </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-17: Honeymoon Day2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-17/</guid>
      <description>Take a walk in London We had a little bit jet lag, so we were going to relax and take a walk in London. And we&amp;rsquo;d like to buy gifts in return.
London is a huge and advanced city, however, London has buildings from the Middle Ages. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing and attractive city.
Shopping We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what to buy as gifts yet, so we were going to go window-shopping at Soho and Regent Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1 in London</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16-london/</guid>
      <description>Immigration I got a little bit nervous at immigration, because I usually get asked many questions at the immigration examination and I can&amp;rsquo;t answer well.
This time, however, immigration officers are very kind. Moreover, my wife said &amp;ldquo;This is our honeymoon&amp;rdquo; then, they said to us &amp;ldquo;Conguraturations!&amp;rdquo; with smile.
Tube We went to the center of London city by Tube: it&amp;rsquo;s subway in London. To ride Tube, we bought Oyster card at the station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-04-16: Honeymoon Day1</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-04-16/</guid>
      <description>The day before depature We decided to carry out our luggage by Sagawa Express to the Handea airport. The luggage was to be carried by the carrier the day before. Until the day I was very busy with packing.
That day I could not sleep much because of excitement.
The depature day, at the airport The plane we were to ride was at 11:35. We wanted to arrive at the airport two hours ago, so we left home at 7:30.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>