<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English self-learning on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english-self-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English self-learning on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 09:28:13 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english-self-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-08: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-08-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 09:28:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-08-english/</guid>
      <description>The last weekend I felt sick the last weekend and yesterday. I watched movies, read a book and got enough sleep. Moreover I canceled the English class yesterday I was going to have. Anyway, I feel better and I could work from home today, I feel bit listless though. I am good enough to be able to have English class today.
I get sick a once or twice a year. This time was the second sick of this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-05: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-05-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 09:38:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-05-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 67-70   They don&amp;rsquo;t look busy.
  What did he put on the table?
  He isn&amp;rsquo;t good at telling jokes.
  Do you remember the night when we went to that party?
  Since she felt sick, she didn&amp;rsquo;t go out.
  Although the man is old, he is stronger than you.
  The girl whose father is a writer likes reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-04: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-04-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 09:38:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-04-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 2020/12/04 lesson: Everyday Idioms (Patience and Nervousness) Homework My wife often complains about her boss. She said that he sometimes jumps the gun and makes mistakes. Moreover, her boss can&amp;rsquo;t sit tight until others finish speaking. When a staff is taking her own sweet time reporting the progress, he is about to get pissed off. Therefore other staffs are always wound up. He is like trying staffs&#39; patience. She was on edge to change her job and then she was decided to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-03: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-03-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 09:37:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-03-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 2020/12/03 lesson: Business English Presentation Introduction Mochi dessert in Ise-city There are a lot of kind of Mochi desserts in Japan. Which Mochi dessert do you like?
Ladies and gentleman, thank you for coming today.
My name is Naoki Morita and I was born and grew up in Ise-city, Mie prefecture in Japan.
Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to speak about Mochi desserts.
Because Ise city, which is my hometown, has a variety of Mochi desserts and I&amp;rsquo;d like you to know my hometown&amp;rsquo;s speciality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-02: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-02-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 09:35:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-02-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 2020/12/02 lesson: Discuss about medicine Notes  Elaborate my opinion. Explain more examples and situations which support the opinion. Use idioms and phrasal verbs that I learned so far. I can remember and use them naturally using them frequently.  How are older people viewed in my country? Elderly people are basically respected in Japan. Because Confucianism affected Japanese for a long time. In fact, Japan has the Respect for the aged day as a national holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-12-01: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-01-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 09:43:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-12-01-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 2020/12/01 lesson Review 2 syllable stress and N/Ng sound
Create a short paragraph about my hobby and wish My hobby is mainly surfing. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of surfing because I feel nature power and the smooth surface of the wave during riding waves. My wife and I used to go camping before this pandemic, however in these days we don&amp;rsquo;t. Because nowadays many campers go camping, so campsites is very crowded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-30: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-30-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 09:43:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-30-english/</guid>
      <description>News: Thousands of Argentinians say goodbye to Maradona 29th November, 2020 Thousands of football fans paid their final respects to football legend Diego Maradona on Thursday. Huge crowds lined the streets of the capital Buenos Aires to catch a glimpse of the car carrying his body. The car was draped in the Argentina flag and a football shirt bearing his trademark number 10. Thousands more silently walked past his coffin as it was put on public display at the Presidential Palace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-29: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-29-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 23:07:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-29-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Part2 Second round (1, 2, 3)  Talk about your best memory of traveling.  My best memory of traveling was my honeymoon. My wife and I went to England, Scotland, Canada and America for about a month. We had much delicious food and enjoyed a lot of beautiful scenery. Finally I introduced my wife to my brother who lives with his family in America. It was a very good memory of traveling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-28: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-28-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 23:19:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-28-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 62-66   This is the most funny funniest joke I&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard.
  A The young person who broke the statue was punished.
  The day when he goes to the town is Tuesday.
  Tomorrow it will be as cold as today.
  They didn&amp;rsquo;t leave until he arrived.
  He told taught them how to use the machine.
  He went to the bookstore to buy a magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-27: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-27-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-27-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/27 lesson: Discussion How To Create A Career
Notes There are three points to be improved in this class. First, I ought to speak further. For instance, I should expand my opinion adding reason, examples, or feeling. Second, I&amp;rsquo;d better less thinking time. Because it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to respond quickly in general conversation. Finally, I might want to deliver a topic of small talk spontaneously. I should enjoy a conversation positively, not be always a passive attitude in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-26: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-26-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-26-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/26 lesson: EVERYDAY IDIOMS Unit 04 Notes I&amp;rsquo;d better use &amp;ldquo;even though&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;instead&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;moreover&amp;rdquo; for conjunction, not &amp;ldquo;so&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo;.
Have you ever been stuck in a traffic? Yes, I have. I&amp;rsquo;ve been stuck in a traffic during consecutive holidays. Because there are several consecutive holidays in Japan. As the result, many Japanese go on a trip at the same time. Once you were caught in a traffic jam, you can&amp;rsquo;t pick up the speed and you have to inch along even if you were in a hurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-25: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-25-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-25-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Scientists say they can reverse ageing process - 25th November, 2020 Scientists in Israel say they have conducted tests to successfully stop and reverse the biological ageing process. The tests were part of a joint project by Tel Aviv University and the Shamir Medical Center. The researchers said the science behind their experiments was very simple - they used only oxygen to slow down and turn around what happens to cells as they age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-24: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-24-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-24-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/24 lesson Homework: make sentences using at least 4 phrasal verbs about cleaning When I was a child, I was not good at clearing up my room. Contrarily, my mother is neat and tidy, so she couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand my dirty room. Thus, she often told me to tidy up my room and sweep it up at least once a week. Now I am better organized than before. I always hang up my jacket when I come back, so my clothes are never jumbled up on the floor or the bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-23: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-23-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-23-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/23 lesson: TED(Keep Your Goals To Yourself) Vocabulary conventional always following the behaviour and attitudes that most people in a society consider to be normal, right, and socially acceptable, so that you seem slightly boring
 I don&amp;rsquo;t like a conventional way, because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make me improve. There are many conventional phrases in the newspaper, so I am sometimes bored with it.  conventional wisdom the opinion that most people consider to be normal and right, but that is sometimes shown to be wrong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-22: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-22-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 15:00:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-22-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(57-61)   Why did he paint this picture?
  The news will surprise them.
  A woman whose name was Nancy Brown came here today.
  The vegetables sold here are fresh.
  Bob must know her phone number.
  Did you see the program again?
 Yes, I did.    It will be cloudy in Paris tomorrow.
  The teacher took the students to the museum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-21: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-21-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:02:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-21-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(57-61)   The news will surprise them.
  Did you watch the program again?
 Yes, I did.    The cat is called Tama.
  The teacher took the students to the museum.
  Bob must know her phone number.
  When he told us about the plan, it sounded impossible.
  It will be cloudy in Paris tomorrow.
  A woman whose name is was Nancy Brown came here today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-20: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-20-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 09:21:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-20-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/20 lesson: Discussion culture If you were to create a Christmas tradition in Japan, what would you make? I would make a Christmas tradition that the family gather and eat Nabe. Nabe is a stew and soup served in winter, and the dish is frequently cooked at the table. The diners can pick the cooked ingredients they want from the pot. The family can spend wonderful time through Nabe. On the other hand, nowadays many Japanese eat KFC&amp;rsquo;s chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-19: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-19-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 09:34:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-19-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/19 lesson: Business telephoning Practice  callee: Thank you for calling ABC Corporation.  This is Morita speaking. How can I help you?   caller:  I would like to speak to Ms.XXX please.   callee: May I have your name, please? caller:  This is YYY.   callee: Could you spell that for me, please? caller: Y.Y.Y callee:  Can I have your company name, please?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-18: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-18-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 09:49:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-18-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Part2 (76, 77, 78) Explain about the time why you couldn’t express your opinion well.  I can&amp;rsquo;t always express my opinion well in English classes. Because I can&amp;rsquo;t still speak English well in spite of studying English everyday. For instance, I can&amp;rsquo;t express well what I felt about something or why I did such a thing, something like that. That is, it&amp;rsquo;s usual not to express my opinion well in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-17: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-17-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:59:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-17-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/17 lesson: pronunciation flap t and soft d Examples using flap t When I became thirties and forties, I noticed that aging has already started. I would better go to hospital for checking my health. In adiition, I ought to eat more vegetables like lettus and less butter. Moreover, I&amp;rsquo;d btter do more exercise since I&amp;rsquo;m always sitting and using a computer and internet.
T: flap t = /d/  better university hostiptal middle thirty forty shorter sweeter water pretty city a lot of out of computer internet little putting letter lettuce what a good diea what are you doing ought to got to wanted started daughter painted British butter bitter sitting notice   Writing: Part2 (76, 77, 78) Explain about the time why you couldn’t express your opinion well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-16: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-16-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 10:37:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-16-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/16 lesson: Discussion Mental Models and Making Decisions You Don’t Regret
Notes  Answer compound questions respectively and concisely. Use prepositions correctly and make sentences understandably.  Vocabulary hindsight the ability to understand a situation only after it has happened
 With hindsight, I could have done something good unless I was lazy with many things. With hindsight, I had many things that I feel there had to be a better way to do them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-15: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-15-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 18:30:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-15-english/</guid>
      <description>Preparation for discussion class Mental Models and Making Decisions You Don’t Regret
beginning We tend to overlook cases that did not come with a successful outcome. And when we do look at failure, we are often quick to explain why things failed.
Bad Decisions and Good Decisions Failure is not always explained by bad decision making. “Good decisions can lead to bad outcomes and vice versa.”
Mental Models: Focus On The Process, Not The Outcome By simply focusing on the thinking process, we can always say we did the right thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-14: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-14-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 08:25:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-14-english/</guid>
      <description>Listening: 3-24 TW 17 telephone system
Mode.1  TW-17 telephone has the functions below.  An automatically direction of call An audio and video meeting A directed fax function   You can share documents during conversation using this system. It has additional options below.  It can recall playback messages. It can display all telephone numbers you called and received before.    Mode.2  TW-17 telephone has the functions below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-13: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-13-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 09:47:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-13-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/13 lesson: TED Vocabulary elaborate: verb to give more details or new information about something
 It is sometimes boring to elaborate what I do on weekdays, because there is nothing special usually. Elaborate about what you can&amp;rsquo;t understand, or I don&amp;rsquo;t say anything. I ought to elaborate my opinion to add examples, descriptions or feeling in general conversation.  put/poke your nose down in something to take an interest or get involved in something</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-12: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-12-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 09:38:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-12-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/12 lesson: Phrasal verbs Unit 12 - Yvee take
Vocabulary and the examples take sth apart to separate something into all its different parts
 It&amp;rsquo;s fun to take something apart. However, take pictures of your progress or you can&amp;rsquo;t put them back. I dropped my glass and it was taken apart. He got angry with the newspaper, so he took it apart.  take sth/sb aside to separate something/somebody away from a group</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-11: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-11-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 09:56:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-11-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Kamala Harris to be first woman Vice President - 9th November, 2020 Kamala Harris is the U.S. Vice Presidentelect. The major television networks in the USA have announced that Joe Biden has won the 2020 U.S. Election. They said Mr Biden has 279 votes in the Electoral College, which is enough for him to be elected as America&amp;rsquo;s 46th President. Ms Harris will be the first woman in U.S. history to hold the post of Vice President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-10: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-10-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 09:26:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-10-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/10 lesson bring out to produce something that will be sold to the public
 Linkin Park haven&amp;rsquo;t brought out a new album since the singer&amp;rsquo;s death. Apple brought out new Macbook Pro a few month ago. The company is going to bring out a new product next month.  turn out to produce or make a lot of a particular product
 It&amp;rsquo;s normal now to turn out thousands of commodities by a lots of machinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-09: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-09-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 14:57:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-09-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/09 lesson: Discussion - current event 8 politics ? Notes  Don&amp;rsquo;t use &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s it&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; in the end of my opinion. Remember &amp;ldquo;OREO&amp;rdquo; method when I express my opinion.  Vocabulary decade a period of ten years
 A CD I bought for the first time was named &amp;ldquo;Decade of Decadence&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;Motley Crue&amp;rdquo;. I have worked as a software engineer for more decade.  sworn in got someone to do a job by making them promise to do a job</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-08: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-08-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 13:17:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-08-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(47-51)   I don&amp;rsquo;t want to say anything now.
  Her daughter graduated from high school this year.
  He has lost the pictures he took in France.
  He was kind enough to help me do with my homework.
  Did he eat it with chopsticks?
  He saw the leaves fall down.
  He can swim faster than Tom.
  Look at the picture hanging on the wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-07: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-07-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 13:16:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-07-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Stress baking helped during U.S. election - 5th November, 2020 The 2020 U.S. presidential election was a stressful event for many people. A poll conducted by the marketing research company OnePoll found that the election was a main cause of stress in 49 per cent of people. Only COVID19 caused greater stress. The poll found that 55 per cent of the 2,000 adults in the survey believed that November the 3rd, 2020 would be the tensest day yet this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-06: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-06-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 11:58:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-06-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/06 lesson: Discussion about rich-mind Notes I should use &amp;ldquo;OREO&amp;rdquo; when I deliver my opinion.
Vocabulary and the examples isolate  It&amp;rsquo;s important for us to isolate facts and opinions. If I go to America, when I come back to Japan I have to be isolated not to infect others with coronavirus. I feel isolated in spite of surrounded with many people.  lack  Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of lack of experience, you can do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-05: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-05-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 09:54:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-05-english/</guid>
      <description>English 11/05 lesson Receive the e-mail Dear Mr. Nao, A pleasant evening to you Mr. Nao. I hope you are doing well in spite of this very busy week. I am writing to inform you about our meeting this Monday, November 9 2020 in the afternoon.
We are going to discuss about the new software updates. In regards to this, I would like you to prepare a short report about the new system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-04: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-04-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:50:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-04-english/</guid>
      <description>Breaking News: Diet drinks may be as unhealthy as sugary ones - 1st November, 2020 Many people drink diet sodas as part of their diet. They believe these drinks are healthier than fizzy drinks. However, according to a new study, &amp;ldquo;diet&amp;rdquo; versions of sugary drinks can be as bad for our heart as fizzy drinks that are loaded with sugar. The researchers who conducted the study said people should avoid diet sodas and other artificially sweetened beverages if they want to look after their health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-03: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-03-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 10:38:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-03-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/03 lesson What I must be careful with  /z/ sound smooth &amp;ldquo;ng&amp;rdquo; at middle of a word word stress  My favorite hobby using N and NG sounds My favorite hobby is surfing. Surfing is amazing and outstanding. Because I can feel freedom and be a part of nature during riding waves. For instance, I feel like flying on the wave. Even when I am waiting for coming waves, I can hear sounds like singing from the sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-02: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-02-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 13:34:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-02-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 11/02 lesson Phrasal verbs and the examples(time) put sb/sth off  to delay doing something or to arrange to do something at a later time or date, especially because there is a problem or you do not want to do it now  The boxing match was put off because the champion was infected with coronavirus. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to put the schedule off anymore. Would you put the date of the meeting off until next Tuesday?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-11-01: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-01-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 16:25:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-11-01-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Part2 (63, 65, 66) What is your opinion about banning smoking in public?  I agree with banning smoking in public. Because smoking gives both smokers and non-smokers bad effects. For instance, smoke brings a cancer even if non-smokers breath cigarette smoke. Therefore, smokers must smoke in a smoking room, not in public.   Do you think your workplace is woman-friendly?  I don&amp;rsquo;t think my workplace is woman-friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-31: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-31-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 11:33:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-31-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: Part2 (60, 61, 62) Explain the steps of online shopping.  First, you choose a product you want. Second, you put it in your cart. Thirdly, you select how to pay for it. Finally, you specify the date when you want it to be delivered. That&amp;rsquo;s all.   What do you do gather information for work?  I&amp;rsquo;ll explain when I meet with a software bug. First, I comprehend the error messages the bug outputs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-30: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-30-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 09:39:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-30-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/30 lesson Idioms Number and Quantity
Idioms and the examples at least, at most  I want to sell my keyboard at least fifty dollars, however it will be twenty dollars at most. It will take at least 20 minutes to get there, however I have only 15 minutes at most until the exam. I need at least a thousand yen more to buy it. I can bring more ten kilo gram at most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-29: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-29-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 09:38:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-29-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/29 lesson My saying or quotes My saying is &amp;ldquo;Run full speed ahead shutting your eyes&amp;rdquo;. I mean you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of the future and do your best. Nobody can see the future, it&amp;rsquo;s like shutting your eyes. If you shut your eyes, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to care even if someone is laughing at you. Of course, you will fall down on some obstacles, however it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter in your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-28: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-28-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:49:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-28-english/</guid>
      <description>Breaking Nes: UK government votes against free meals for poorer children The UK government voted against giving poor children free school lunches during the school holidays. Only five politicians in the ruling Conservative party voted to help poorer children with a daily lunch. A huge majority of the government voted against the weekly $20-perchild food voucher. The government is now under pressure to make a U-turn. It made a U-turn in the summer over free school meals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-27: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-27-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 09:39:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-27-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/27 lesson I should use positive words in a job interview. Moreover, I&amp;rsquo;d better tell my experience and achievement.
a. Answering questions about your weakness My weakness is that I&amp;rsquo;m eager to use new technology or method I&amp;rsquo;ve never done at work. Because I want to improve my skills while improving my skill. On the other hand, to solve a problem doesn&amp;rsquo;t always require new technology or method. Therefore, at first I make a plan to solve a problem and have my colleagues review it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-26: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-26-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:57:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-26-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/26 lesson Source: https://wanderwisdom.com/misc/Ten-Basic-Differences-Between-the-USA-and-Europe
Vocabulary and examples using the vocabulary patriotic:adj (patriotism:noun) having or expressing a great love of your country
 Rather than I&amp;rsquo;m not very patriotic, I don&amp;rsquo;t like inflaming people&amp;rsquo;s patriotism. It seems to me that most of American are patriotic. I don&amp;rsquo;t have patriotic spirit, but I love my family, friends, and neighborhoods.  outspoken (outspokenness: noun) expressing your opinions honestly and directly, even when doing this might annoy some people</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-25: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-25-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 13:53:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-25-english/</guid>
      <description>Breaking News: Eating jellyfish could save endangered fish 24th October, 2020 Scientists think they have found an answer to the problem of food shortages. One solution could be for us to eat jellyfish. This could also help to protect fish and other sea life that are endangered. Researchers from the University of Queensland in Australia conducted a study of fishing around the world. They discovered that fishing nets caught 92 endangered species of seafood and 11 species of marine life classed as &amp;ldquo;critically endangered&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-24: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-24-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 15:07:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-24-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 38-41   This is a toy which is loved by children all over the world.
  Although the traffic sign lights turned red, the car didn&amp;rsquo;t stop.
  She has never heard her husband speak English.
  The milk was too hot for her to drink.
  Have you ever eaten Spanish cuisine?
  What time are you going to get up tomorrow?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-23: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-23-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:50:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-23-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/23 lesson I got the rules for the stress of two syllables. I sometimes mispronounce it, though. Because it takes bit time to understand the meaning of the sentence.
Vocabulary desert = abandon to leave someone or something and no longer help or support them
 I wonder Mr.Trump will be deserted by most voters at the next election. People desert a criminal in the desert to punish him. They didn&amp;rsquo;t permit him to drink water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-22: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-22-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 10:12:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-22-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/22 lesson What I wanted to say but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t say I would like to make beef brisket using slow cooker. Because the brisket cooked by slow cooker is super soft and juicy.
what I felt difficult Phrasal verbs of &amp;lsquo;make&amp;rsquo; have lots of meanings and it seems that they are used in limited situations. So, it was not easy for me to imagine such situations and make sentences using those idioms at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-21: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-21-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 09:27:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-21-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: World&amp;rsquo;s largest refugee camp must stay open 11th February, 2017 Article The High Court in Kenya has blocked the Kenyan government&amp;rsquo;s attempt to close the largest refugee camp in the world. The Dadaab camp houses 330,000 refugees. Kenya&amp;rsquo;s government wanted to close it and send 260,000 Somali refugees back to Somalia. The High Court decided it was wrong to send the Somalis back just because of their nationality. A judge said: &amp;ldquo;The government&amp;rsquo;s decision specifically targeting Somali refugees is an act of group persecution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-20: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-20-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 09:35:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-20-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/20 lesson Discussion URL: http://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/13711387
Summary Residents of Tokyo who moved out of the capital outnumbered those who moved in after this pandemic. On the other hand, the opposite happened in local cities. Because people was afraid of infection with coronavirus.
In addition, they don&amp;rsquo;t have to stay in big cities any more now. Because they can work from home or attend classes remotely. The experts says this trend is likely to keep staying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-19: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-19-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 09:36:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-19-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/19 lesson Idioms and examples using the idioms If possible, I want to be able to speak English well in no time. However, I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to speak all of a sudden without huge efforts. I&amp;rsquo;ve studied English so far but I can&amp;rsquo;t still.
Nowadays you may be able to have a translator device to communicate with foreigners right away, but you&amp;rsquo;d better to keep learning English in the long run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-18: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-18-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:33:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-18-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(34-37)   Does the milk taste sour?
 No, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t.    My father likes taking pictures of flowers.
  Let Bob read the book.
  I found the movie very interesting.
  When I was doing my homework yesterday, my brother helped me.
  The story he wrote was very interesting.
  Walk as slowly as you can.
  Tell Tom to come her at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-17: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-17-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 18:47:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-17-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(34-37)   Let Bob read the book.
  I found the movie very interesting.
  The story he wrote was very interesting.
  Walk as slowly as you can.
  Tell Tom to come here at once.
  Mr.Brown is going to come to this town next week.
  When I was doing my homework yesterday, my brother helpd me.
  Is the milk sour?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-16: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-16-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 09:32:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-16-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/16 lesson Vocabulary and Examples using the vocabulary exceed to be more than a particular number or amount
 My current weight doesn&amp;rsquo;t exceed that one from a month ago. The presentation was so great that exceeded my expectation.  simmer to boil gently, or to cook something slowly by boiling it gently
 You simmer a block of beef at low-temperature for a long time and then it will become very soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-15: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-15-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 09:25:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-15-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/15 lesson Review words connections.
 consonant-consonant consonant-vowel vowel-vowel  I learned omitting /h/ sound when linking. But it was difficult for me to hear the words include such linking all at once. Once I got used to the pronunciation of the recorded voice, I was able to hear it a little better. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep practice to listen.
Speaking: 4-36 Try.1  There are two cats on her bed.  Two cats is on her bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-14: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-14-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 09:11:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-14-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/14 lesson Vocabulary I was looking for an interesting destination. After going around many tourist&amp;rsquo;s web sites, I came to a destination. It was a Miyako island of Okinawa.
look for somebody/something = search for  to try to find something that you have lost, or someone who is not where they should be  Recently I really often look for what I put somewhere a little while ago. I became forgetful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-13: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-13-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 09:39:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-13-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-34 Try.1  My brother helped me, when I was doing my homework yesterday. Mr. Brown is going to come to this town next week. Let Bob to read the book. I&amp;rsquo;m the happiest man in the world now. I found the movie was very interesting. Walk as slowly as possible. Is the milk sour?  ~~No, it isn&amp;rsquo;t.`~ Does the milk taste sour? No, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t.   Tell Tom to come here now at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-12: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-12-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 09:09:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-12-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/12 lesson What I wanted to say but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t say Talk about your favorite restaurant My favorite restaurant is a pub that a brewery manages in my city. You can drink several types of sake and beer that the brewery made. I like sake especially &amp;ldquo;Junmai Ginjo&amp;rdquo; because it smells good and tasty. &amp;ldquo;Junmai Ginjo&amp;rdquo; means that the sake is made of rice, malted rice and water. In addition, the rice is polished to remove its surface, as a result it has fruity flavor and soft texture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-11: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-11-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 13:51:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-11-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 10/11 lesson /y/ sound linking a  May I help you? Could you say it again, please? I don&amp;rsquo;t lay out a map, use a smartphone&amp;rsquo;s app. We have to lay over this event indefinitely due to this pandemic.  e  He is very old, but he smokes and drinks. She is the best teacher for me. We are friends, aren&amp;rsquo;t we. I finally agreed with the plan.  i  He asked to help him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-10: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-10-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 13:55:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-10-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-[30-33]   They&amp;rsquo;re going to stay at the hotel next week.
  I have a lot of things to learn.
  The boy was pale.
  Has the boy been become as tall as his father yet?
 Yes, he has.    How old was he when he wrote that poem?
  I wonder what flower that is.
  He is always with Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-09: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-09-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 09:12:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-09-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-33 Try.1  Are they in at the library now?  No, they aren&amp;rsquo;t.   Your grandfather is too old to go there. Would you tell me what she wants, please?  Please tell me what she wants.   How many books did Tom read last year? The article written by her was long. She had many thing to do yesterday. How beautiful this lake is! The foreigner I met at the party last night spoke Japanese so well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-08: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-08-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:27:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-08-english/</guid>
      <description>Today It&amp;rsquo;s raining all this week. Because a typhoon is coming.
Speaking: 4-32 Try.1  This cake was cooked/made by Nancy. They named their daughter as Alice. Yesterday I met him in front of the station.  I saw him in front of the station yesterday.   What language is he talking?  What is the language he is speaking?   Do you think this is a good plan?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-07: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-07-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 09:34:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-07-english/</guid>
      <description>Today I worked from home as usual. It&amp;rsquo;s getting dark earlier. Now sunrise is at five thirty and sunset is at around five. By the way, a typhoon is coming. So, waves are getting bigger. It&amp;rsquo;s good to surf. Rainy or sunny doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter for suring. That&amp;rsquo;s the nice thing about surfing. I don&amp;rsquo;t like jogging under rain. However, I don&amp;rsquo;t care about rain during surfing.
Speaking: 4-31 Try.1  They believe she will come on the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-06: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-06-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 09:32:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-06-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-30 Try.1  They are going to stay at the hotel next week. Who opened the door? The boy was pale. I have many things to learn. He&amp;rsquo;s always with Tom. I wonder what flower that is. That is the restaurant which is opened last month. Has the boy already become as tall as his father yet?  Yes, he has.   How old is was he when he wrote that poem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-05: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-05-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 09:49:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-05-english/</guid>
      <description>How am I donig today? I&amp;rsquo;m doing good. Last Saturday, I had my hair cut. I feel my head became lighter than before. And it&amp;rsquo;s good for surfing.
Did I mention my plan to go on a trip to Okinawa before? I&amp;rsquo;m decided to go on a trip to Okinawa next January. My wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday is in January. The reason I decided to go on the trip is because I&amp;rsquo;m little bored of staying home and I want to go somewhere with Japanese government support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-04: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-04-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 15:15:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-04-english/</guid>
      <description>Sepaking: 4-(26-29) Traiing (26-29) Try.1   She went back to England for Christmas.
  That woman can speak twenty languages.
  I think she is older than Tom.
  What he said may be true.
  That cat which is sleeping on the sofa is Tama.
  Peter is the tallest student in this school.
  She is as beautiful as a rose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-03: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-03-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 13:47:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-03-english/</guid>
      <description>Sepaking: 4-(26-29) Traiing (26-29) Try.1   It is true that he said.
 What he said may be true.    The cat which is sleeping on the sofa is Tama.
  She is as beautiful as a rose.
  That woman can speak twenty languages.
  Peter is the tallest student in this school.
  When did he go to India?
  I think that she is older than Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-02: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-02-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 09:37:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-02-english/</guid>
      <description>Sepaking: 4-29 Traiing 29 Try.1  I want you to listen to this song once again. Bob&amp;rsquo;s car was out of order in a way to there.  Bob&amp;rsquo;s car broke down on the way there.   That is the a chair my son made. I want to take my wife to Paris. You must not smoke here. Where did your daughter find this book? She will never see them again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-01: English Review</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-01-english-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 23:42:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-01-english-review/</guid>
      <description>Review today&amp;rsquo;s lesson Vocabulary Phrasal verbs  come over  to visit someone at their house   come along  to go somewhere with someone   come apart/off  to become separated or removed from something   come off  if something that has been planned comes off, it happens to be successful   come around/round  (America) become conscious again after you have been unconscious (British) to visit someone at their house (British) to change your opinion so that you now agree with someone or are no longer angry with them   come out  if something comes out, it is removed from a place if information comes out, people learn about it, especially after it has been kept secret if a photograph comes out, it shows a clear picture if a book, record etc comes out, it becomes publicly available   come about  to happen, especially in a way that is not planned   come up  if a subject comes up, people mention it and discuss it if a problem or difficulty comes up, it appears or starts to affect you if a job or an opportunity comes up, it becomes available   come up against something/somebody  to have to deal with problems or difficulties   come across somebody/something  to meet, find, or discover someone or something by chance   come down  to accept a lower price to fail to the ground   come to  come to a decision/conclusion/agreement etc to decide something, agree on something etc after considering or discussing a situation    Examples using phrasal verbs I learned  come over  I rarely ask my friends to come over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-10-01: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-01-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 10:55:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-10-01-english/</guid>
      <description>Sepaking: 4-28 Traiing 28 Try.1  The girl had a busket basket which is was full of flowers. Where did you see his sister? She prefers Winter to Summer.  She likes winter better than summer.   What did he say somthing?  Did he say antyhing?   Were there a lot of things in that town that you should see?  Were there many things to see in that town?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-30: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-30-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 08:12:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-30-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-27 Training 27 Try.1  I have never read the poem. She saw lookep up at the shining star. That is the man everyone in the town respects. Why did Tom eat nothing yesterday? It will be so fun that you study in this school.  It will be a lot of fun to study at this school.   He had enough money to buy the house. You must do your homework before you watch TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-29: English Listeing&amp;Writing</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-29-english-ls-wr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 23:09:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-29-english-ls-wr/</guid>
      <description>Listening Unit 4 Mode.1  He hasn&amp;rsquo;t been very effective either domestic or international issues. The next president should handling with the following things.  domestic issue national security education international relation crime employment violence credit   Because the education system isn&amp;rsquo;t working.  Mode.2  He thinks that the president hasn&amp;rsquo;t been very effective either domestic or international issues. The think that the next president should do something about the following things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-29: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-29-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 11:42:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-29-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/29 lesson Vocabulary  stuck in a rut  too fixed in one particular type of job, activity, method, etc., and needing to change   habit  something that you do often and regularly, sometimes without knowing that you are doing it   dwelling  a house or place to live in   nerd  a person, especially a man, who is not attractive and is awkward or socially embarrassing   deprived  not having the things that are necessary for a pleasant life, such as enough money, food, or good living conditions    Examples using the vocabulary If you feel stuck in a rut, you&amp;rsquo;d better to break your bad habit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-28: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-28-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 09:09:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-28-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: Unit21-25   When did it begin to snow?
  Is that old man his grandfather?
 Yes, he is.    The girl riding the horse is Emily.
  I know all of them.
  She will never forget the man who she met at the party.
  This is a poem written by a famous poet.
  The movie that we watched last week was very interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-27: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-27-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 13:25:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-27-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/25 Lesson Homework  What are the advantages and disadvantages of virtual tourism?  The advantages of it is that you can go everywhere you want to. The disadvantage of it is that you can&amp;rsquo;t touch anything in there.    Vocabulary  curvatures revitalize employ conformal account for in person  Today I&amp;rsquo;m relaxed today. I was watching the TV drama series, Friends. I want to watch it without subtitles, however I can&amp;rsquo;t yet now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-26: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-26-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 18:56:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-26-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-25 Training 25 Try.1  How many roses did you he buy there? He went to drink with his friends last night.  He went for a drink with his friends last night.   Who woke up the baby? Do you know someone anyone who can speak English and Chinese?  Do you know anyone who can speak English and Chinese?   When did Mr.Brown quit smoking?  When did Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-25: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-25-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 11:48:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-25-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-24 Training 24 Try.1  Is he taking a shower?  No, he isn&amp;rsquo;t.   This stone is heavier than that one. Did you eat meat yesterday? Do you want to go to the sea in this afternoon?  Yes, I do.   My husband enjoys listening to jazz before sleeping he goes to bed. I come home before seven o&amp;rsquo;clock.  I will be home before seven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-24: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-24-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 09:13:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-24-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/21 Lesson The Greatest Wealth is Health You can&amp;rsquo;t do anything if you are unhealthy. Unhealthiness demotivate you and you can&amp;rsquo;t do even what you like. Even If you were so rich that you can buy everything, you can&amp;rsquo;t buy your health. Therefore, people say that the greatest wealth is health.
Vocabulary  nutritional  relating to the substances in food that help you to stay healthy   regardless  without being affected or influenced by something   significant  having an important effect or influence, especially on what will happen in the future   induce  to cause a particular physical condition   demotivate  to make people less willing to do their job    Examples of using vocabulary I learned I&amp;rsquo;m learning new technology regardless of my task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-23: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-23-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 09:26:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-23-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-22 Training 22 Try.1  Who is the pretty girl whom you were talking to? What were you doing with him at that time then? This work is so important that we must finish it first.  As this work is very important, we have to finish it first.   Do Can you see the dog running in the park?  Can you see the dog which running in the park?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-22: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-22-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 20:18:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-22-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-21 Training 21 Try.1  I know all of them. She was doing the her homework in her room at that time. The movie that we watched last week was very interesting. When did it begin to snow? She will not ever never forget the man who she met at the party. Is the that old man his grandfather?  Yes, he is.   This is the poem that the famous poet wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 09 21 English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-21-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 13:25:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-21-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: 23rd February, 2020 - Big breakfasts help us burn double the calories Discussion  a) What do you think of your weight?  I think I would better reduce my weight. Because my weight is heavier than the average people who are the same height as I. However, in my opinion, even if you have more weight, it&amp;rsquo;s good provided that you&amp;rsquo;re healthy and feeling good. Because it&amp;rsquo;s important not only to be physical healthy but also mental healthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-20: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-20-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 17:47:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-20-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/18 lesson Home work I can&amp;rsquo;t read the article unless you allow me to read it.
 In Singapore, the word &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; is considered impolite.  Yes, it is. Because they will sometimes say &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo; to avoid causing offence.   In Greece, you should nod your head upwards to say &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo;  No, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. Because the Greeks traditionally nod the head upwards to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo;. They use a tilt of the head from side to side to mean &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-19: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-19-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-19-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing 18th September, 2020 - Photo of Andromeda Galaxy wins astronomy prize. Summary A French photographer has won a top photography contest. He used a special technique called tilt-shift to take his photo. We can see the Andromeda galaxy bright and close clearly.
Discussion  a) What do you know about astronomy?  I don&amp;rsquo;t know about astronomy very much. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t interested in astronomy when I was a child, and now neither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-18: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-18-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 15:48:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-18-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/18 Lesson They are what I couldn&amp;rsquo;t say what I wanted to say.
Why did the current prime minister of Japan quit? It&amp;rsquo;s because he has a health problem and it has been worse, so he decided not to keep his post. He has been the prime minister before at once, it was fourteen years ago. He resigned from his post at that time because of his health problem. That is to say, he resigned twice from the prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-17: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-17-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 09:08:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-17-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-19 Training 19 Try.1  Tom is the youngest among the three.  Tom was the youngest of the three.   Those children are very smart. Treat Betty kind.  Be nice to Betty.   Why did you tell your wife such a thing?  Why did you say such a thing to your wife?   France is the contry where my wife wants to go. I read this book twice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-16: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-16-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 14:07:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-16-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-18 Training 18 Try.1  He went to Spain to watch see a soccer games. She earns more money than her husband. This is the bag which my grandfather bought for me. Is it cool now in Japan?  Yes, it is.   He tried to solve the problem again. It&amp;rsquo;s so cold that I want something hot to drink. It was snowing at that night when I and my girlfriend had dinner at the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-15: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-15-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 13:28:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-15-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-17 Training 17 Try.1  Are you with your wife now?  Yes, I am.   Who is the person who runs the fastest in the world?  Who runs the fastest in the world?   Where are you going to go with your wife this night tonight? Are Were there a lot of people in at the party? Does your wife often ask you to take her to a restaurants?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-14: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-14-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 15:57:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-14-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/14 lesson I&amp;rsquo;d like to write down about what I wanted to say in the today&amp;rsquo;s lesson. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t say that at that time because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t organized my opinion and find my words. In today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell a gist of the article that I&amp;rsquo;ve read. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to summarize an article immediately.
How did the pandemic affect your country? I think that the pandemic affected my country badly and it will make us use more Information technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-13: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-13-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 18:22:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-13-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: 12th August, 2020 - Delivery of COVID vaccine needs 8,000 jumbo jets Summary Whenever a vaccine for COVID-19 is created, distributing the vaccine will have three big problems. Firstly, the air cargo industry have no experience that deliver 8,000 flights at once. Scientists says that to transport the vaccine across the globe will require around 8,000 flight planes. Secondly, the vaccine requires keeping at the same temperature throughout its journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-12: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-12-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 11:41:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-12-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-(13-16) Training (13-16) Try.1   After he did his homework, the boy played with his friends at in the park.
  They look very happy.
  Mr.Green lives in the wonderful house that has a beautiful garden.
  Mary is as beautiful as Nancy.
  Does he work longer than the other people?
 Yes, he does.    There will be a lot of people here tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-11: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-11-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 09:36:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-11-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/11 lesson If you were to travel this year, where would you like to go? If I were to travel this year, I&amp;rsquo;d like to go to Iceland. Because Iceland has great nature. For instance it has volcanoes, glaciers, fiord, and aurora. Therefore, I want to go on a trip to Iceland, I can&amp;rsquo;t go there now due to COVID-19, though.
How about if you have these four choices, which would you choose?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-10: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-10-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 09:22:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-10-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/10 lesson I&amp;rsquo;m bad at pronounce /l/ and /r/ sound. I can&amp;rsquo;t recognize the differences between them. So, I need to practice more about that. I&amp;rsquo;ll use englishclub.com for that.
Vocabulary  gum ridge  a ridge that forms the borders of the upper and lower jaws and contains the sockets of the teeth.     Speaking: 4-15 Training 15 Try.1  Is her mother beautiful?  Yes, she is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-09: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-09-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:15:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-09-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-14 Training 14 Try.1  Has Did that boy who speaks English well lived live in America for a long time? What time does your brother usually go to bed? How did you see him?  How did you get to know him?   Who is that tall boy?  He is Peter.   He was running in the park. Who is the oldest person in this village?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-08: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:21:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Speaking 4-13 Training 13 Try.1  He was going to visit his grand-mother that day. Did Do you often stay at this hotel?  Yes, I did do.   Mr. Green lives at the in the wonderful house that have has a beautiful garden. Tell me where you found it. Does he work longer than others the other people?  Yes, he does.   There will be many/a lot of people here tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-07: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-07-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 08:50:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-07-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/07 lesson Why video games are so addictive? It&amp;rsquo;s because people can do what they want to do, I think. Since there are many things that they can&amp;rsquo;t do in the real world. For example, they can climb Everest and fly, and they can become even super heroes. Therefore, they are addicted to video games.
How important are graphics in video games? It&amp;rsquo;s so important for video games to have beautiful graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-06: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-06-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 18:54:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-06-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 09/04 lesson Speech Pattern
OREO  O - in my opinion / I think / It seems like / I don&amp;rsquo;t think / If you ask me / It seems to me that / R - because / as / since / due to E - for example / for instance / a good example is O - In conclusion / so / therefore / to conclude / finally  Vocabulary tariff a tax on goods coming into a country or going out of a country</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-05: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-05-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 16:28:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-05-english/</guid>
      <description>Writing: 6th February, 2019 - We may be able to learn vocabulary while sleeping. Summary We may be able to learn vocabulary while sleeping. Because our brain cells are active for a short period of time even while sleeping. The researchers are thinking that our brain can learn new vocabulary while the period of time.
Discussion  a. How important is sleeping?  It&amp;rsquo;s the most important for us to spend a comfortable day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-04: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-04-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 14:47:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-04-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-12 Training 12 Try.1  Is The girl singing on the stage Nancy? The doll began to move suddenly. The This ring is too expensive for me to buy. Would you paint these walls in white, please? Don&amp;rsquo;t open this door.  You must not open this door.   That language is not spoken now. Where did you buy that sweater? I&amp;rsquo;d like to arrive there before it begins to rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-03: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-03-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 10:01:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-03-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-11 Training 11 Try.1  The cat is was loved by everyone. He can jump higher than you. It is was boring for her to study the subject. This book is hers. Could you take care of my cat, when I leave home?  Will you please take care of my cat while I am away? Would you take care of my cat while I&amp;rsquo;m away?   My son is talking with someone via the telephone now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-02: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-02-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:19:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-02-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: Unit.10 Try.1  After he took a bath, he drank a glass of beer. Do I have to buy this book?  Do I need to buy this book? No, you don&amp;rsquo;t.   Where will you eat dinner?  Where are you going to have dinner?   Don&amp;rsquo;t left leave the door open. The tree is was too high for the boy to climb. He had a the weighter bring a cup glass of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-01: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-01-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 08:40:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-01-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 08/31 lesson. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk well the following things.
 My history about workplace, university and graduate school in my self-introduction Why do I prefer rural to urban?  I began to work at Meguro, Tokyo after graduate school. About two years later, I changed my job. Because I wanted to develop software. I had deployed, managed and operated servers and networks, however, I found that I liked also programming as well as managing networks and servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-30: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-30-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 08:51:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-30-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-9 Training 9 try.1 Writing: 31st August, 2020 - Brain-hacking chip could give up superpowers.  a. My favorite technology trailblazers are Steve Jobs, Jeff Bezos, and of course Elon Musk.  Because they deliver new experiences to us.   b. I don&amp;rsquo;t know him very much. What I know about him are that he manufactures electric vehicles and rockets. c. Yes, it is. I feel it&amp;rsquo;s too fast to catch up with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-29: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-29-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 12:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-29-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-9 Training 9 try.1  The dress is was too big for her to wear. How boring this film is!  what a boring movie this is!   Could you bring us breakfast, please?  Will you please bring us breakfast? Yes, I do. Certainly.   After calling to his wife, he left the office.  He left the office after he called his wife.   Didn&amp;rsquo;t she get surprised?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-28: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-28-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 08:55:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-28-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-8 Training 8 try.1  The garden is covered with flowers. The old man likes taking a walk along with the river after breakfast. She thinks that she is right. I have just cleaned the my room. Haven&amp;rsquo;t you done your homework yet*?  No, I haven&amp;rsquo;t.   Have you been spoken by foreigners?  Have you ever been spoken to by a foreigner?   He was gave a cup of coffee by his daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-27: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-27-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 08:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-27-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-7 Training 7  Your grand mother should will be glad to see you. He is same as smart as you. Call him, or he gets will get angry. Should Must we buy all these books?  Do we have to buy all these books?   What is cheese made from? Do you think that it will rain in the afternoon? Are those girls his daughters?  Yes, they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-26: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-26-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 08:50:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-26-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-6 Training 6  She is too young to live alone. She may be sad. How do did you learn Chinese? Isn&amp;rsquo;t your wife Japanese?  No, she isn&amp;rsquo;t.   What time did he come home?  What time was it when he came back?   Do you see the open window?  Do you see the room the window of which is open?   My brother has been studying Mathematics since he got up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-25: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-25-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 08:04:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-25-english/</guid>
      <description>Review 08/24 lesson Goals  Talk about my daily routine in chronological order. Familiarize phrases or verbs for daily routine. Use the present simple form of the verb in talking about my daily routine.  My routine I&amp;rsquo;m not a morning person, but I usually wake up at around 6:30, because my alarm works snooze function, that is, it alarms again and again. I get up at around 7:00 in the morning, after that I brush my teeth and wash my face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-23: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-23-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:10:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-23-english/</guid>
      <description>1~4. Training-1~4 Writing  Does he know where to go?  Yes, he does.   I went to the library yesterday. Who cooked this?  I did.   They all know the truth. Ellen may be angry. Do I have to read the book?  Yes, you do.   How long have you lived in this country? They began to sing then. My wife wants to go on a trip to Kyoto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-22: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-22-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 11:22:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-22-english/</guid>
      <description>1~4. Training-1~4 Writing  My wife wants to go on a trip to Kyoto. Does he know where to go?  Yes, he does.   I went to the library yesterday. They all know the truth. Who cooked this?  I did.   Ellen may be angry. How long have you lived in this country? Do I have to read this book?  Yes, you do.   Would you pass me the salt, please?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-21: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-21-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 08:33:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-21-english/</guid>
      <description>1-4. Training-4 trial.1  Learning/Studying foreign languages is interesting. Study harder, or you will fail the exam.  Study harder, or you will fail (in) the examination.   How many cups of coffee do you drink a day? Does your dog eat fish? There must be snow in New York.  It must be snowing in New York.   Does Doesn&amp;rsquo;t he speak Japanese?  No, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.   How bright is the star that star is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-20: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-20-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:13:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-20-english/</guid>
      <description>1-3. Training-3 trial.1  He was angry at last.  At last he got angry.   The teacher likes students who study hard. Was he not in his room?  Wasn&amp;rsquo;t he in his room? No, he wasn&amp;rsquo;t.   I made him read the book. How tall the those boys are! He went to a the park to meet see her. They heard that she cried.  They heard her cry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-19: English self-learning</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-19-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:47:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-19-english/</guid>
      <description>1-2. Training-2 trial.1  Is your son tall?  Yes, he is.   Does your sister often go there?  Yes, she does.   Could you show us the picture?  Please show us the picture?   Does he work here?  No, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.   Is she your sister?  No, she isn&amp;rsquo;t.   Jump high as possible as you can.  Jump as high as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-18: English self-learning</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-18-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 08:51:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-18-english/</guid>
      <description>1-1. Training-1 trial.1  Who cooked this?  I do did.   I went to the library yesterday. Does he know where he goes to go?  Yes, he does.   How long have you lived in this country? Ellen may be angry. Could you take me the salt? or Will you please pass me the salt?  Sure.   At that time, they started to sing.  They began to sing then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
