<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English self-learning on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english-self-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English self-learning on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 10:01:20 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/english-self-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-03: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-03-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 10:01:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-03-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 4-11 Training 11 Try.1  The cat is was loved by everyone. He can jump higher than you. It is was boring for her to study the subject. This book is hers. Could you take care of my cat, when I leave home?  Will you please take care of my cat while I am away? Would you take care of my cat while I&amp;rsquo;m away?   My son is talking with someone via the telephone now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-02: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-02-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:19:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-02-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: Unit.10 Try.1  After he took a bath, he drank a glass of beer. Do I have to buy this book?  Do I need to buy this book? No, you don&amp;rsquo;t.   Where will you eat dinner?  Where are you going to have dinner?   Don&amp;rsquo;t left leave the door open. The tree is was too high for the boy to climb. He had a the weighter bring a cup glass of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-01: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-01-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 08:40:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-09-01-english/</guid>
      <description>Review the yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk well the following things.
 My history about workplace, university and graduate school in my self-introduction Why do I prefer rural to urban?  I began to work at Meguro, Tokyo after graduate school. About two years later, I changed my job. Because I wanted to develop software. I had deployed, manage and operate server and network, however, I found that I liked also programming as well as managing network and server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-30: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-30-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 08:51:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-30-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-9 Training 9 try.1 Writing: 31st August, 2020 - Brain-hacking chip could give up superpowers.  a. My favorite technology trailblazers are Steve Jobs, Jeff Bezos, and of course Elon Musk.  Because they deliver new experiences to us.   b. I don&amp;rsquo;t know him very much. What I know about him are that he manufactures electric vehicles and rockets. c. Yes, it is. I feel it&amp;rsquo;s too fast to catch up with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-29: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-29-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 12:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-29-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-9 Training 9 try.1  The dress is was too big for her to wear. How boring this film is!  what a boring movie this is!   Could you bring us breakfast, please?  Will you please bring us breakfast? Yes, I do. Certainly.   After calling to his wife, he left the office.  He left the office after he called his wife.   Didn&amp;rsquo;t she get surprised?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-28: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-28-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 08:55:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-28-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-8 Training 8 try.1  The garden is covered with flowers. The old man likes taking a walk along with the river after breakfast. She thinks that she is right. I have just cleaned the my room. Haven&amp;rsquo;t you done your homework yet*?  No, I haven&amp;rsquo;t.   Have you been spoken by foreigners?  Have you ever been spoken to by a foreigner?   He was gave a cup of coffee by his daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-27: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-27-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 08:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-27-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-7 Training 7  Your grand mother should will be glad to see you. He is same as smart as you. Call him, or he gets will get angry. Should Must we buy all these books?  Do we have to buy all these books?   What is cheese made from? Do you think that it will rain in the afternoon? Are those girls his daughters?  Yes, they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-26: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-26-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 08:50:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-26-english/</guid>
      <description>Speaking: 1-6 Training 6  She is too young to live alone. She may be sad. How do did you learn Chinese? Isn&amp;rsquo;t your wife Japanese?  No, she isn&amp;rsquo;t.   What time did he come home?  What time was it when he came back?   Do you see the open window?  Do you see the room the window of which is open?   My brother has been studying Mathematics since he got up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-25: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-25-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 08:04:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-25-english/</guid>
      <description>Daily Routine Goals  Talk about my daily routine in chronological order. Familiarize phrases or verbs for daily routine. Use the present simple form of the verb in talking about my daily routine.  My routine I&amp;rsquo;m not a morning person, but I usually wake up at around 6:30, because my alarm works snooze function, that is, it alarms again and again. I get up at around 7:00 in the morning, after that I brush my teeth and wash my face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-23: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-23-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:10:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-23-english/</guid>
      <description>1~4. Training-1~4 Writing  Does he know where to go?  Yes, he does.   I went to the library yesterday. Who cooked this?  I did.   They all know the truth. Ellen may be angry. Do I have to read the book?  Yes, you do.   How long have you lived in this country? They began to sing then. My wife wants to go on a trip to Kyoto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-22: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-22-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 11:22:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-22-english/</guid>
      <description>1~4. Training-1~4 Writing  My wife wants to go on a trip to Kyoto. Does he know where to go?  Yes, he does.   I went to the library yesterday. They all know the truth. Who cooked this?  I did.   Ellen may be angry. How long have you lived in this country? Do I have to read this book?  Yes, you do.   Would you pass me the salt, please?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-21: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-21-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 08:33:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-21-english/</guid>
      <description>1-4. Training-4 trial.1  Learning/Studying foreign languages is interesting. Study harder, or you will fail the exam.  Study harder, or you will fail (in) the examination.   How many cups of coffee do you drink a day? Does your dog eat fish? There must be snow in New York.  It must be snowing in New York.   Does Doesn&amp;rsquo;t he speak Japanese?  No, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.   How bright is the star that star is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-20: English</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-20-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:13:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-20-english/</guid>
      <description>1-3. Training-3 trial.1  He was angry at last.  At last he got angry.   The teacher likes students who study hard. Was he not in his room?  Wasn&amp;rsquo;t he in his room? No, he wasn&amp;rsquo;t.   I made him read the book. How tall the those boys are! He went to a the park to meet see her. They heard that she cried.  They heard her cry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-19: English self-learning</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-19-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:47:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-19-english/</guid>
      <description>1-2. Training-2 trial.1  Is your son tall?  Yes, he is.   Does your sister often go there?  Yes, she does.   Could you show us the picture?  Please show us the picture?   Does he work here?  No, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.   Is she your sister?  No, she isn&amp;rsquo;t.   Jump high as possible as you can.  Jump as high as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-18: English self-learning</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-18-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 08:51:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2020-08-18-english/</guid>
      <description>1-1. Training-1 trial.1  Who cooked this?  I do did.   I went to the library yesterday. Does he know where he goes to go?  Yes, he does.   How long have you lived in this country? Ellen may be angry. Could you take me the salt? or Will you please pass me the salt?  Sure.   At that time, they started to sing.  They began to sing then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>