<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aws on naomori&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in aws on naomori&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 09:47:54 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naomori.github.io/journal/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-14: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day3</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 09:47:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-14/</guid>
      <description>Today, I attneded AWS Summit Tokyo 2019: the final day. I used the Shonan Liner and the limited express Wakashio this morning, too. It was so comfortable that I can&#39;t imagine coming to Kaihin Makuhari without getting on the express.
Keynote (10:00-11:30) It was the almost same as the Day 1&#39;s keynote. Furthermore, the presenter talked too much and it was overtime. Panasonic&#39;s speech wasn&#39;t good neither.
 [初級] AWS コンテナサービス入門 (12:00-12:40) The presenter talked very well, so I could understand about the AWS Container Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-13: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day2</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-13/</guid>
      <description>Continuing from yesterday, I attended AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 today, too. This morning I used the Shonan Liner and the limited express Wakashio, so it was comfortable to come to the Kaihin-Makuhari station.
AWS Sumerian (10:00-10:40) AWS Sumerian provides Environments of development and distribution for eXtended Reality(XR). XR represents Virtual Reality(VR), Augmented Reality(AR), and Mixed Reality(MR). A presenter said that the XR Application developed by Sumerian works on various environments. It works with AWS IoT and can display graph of data collected by sensors on AR application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-12: AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 Day1</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 09:44:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-06-12/</guid>
      <description>I attended AWS Summit Tokyo 2019 today. It will be held in 3 days. I&#39;m gonna attend it every days.
Keynote (10:00-11:30) The music was loud at the venue and it was like rock concert, so I was a little excited. The opening of keynote was started with movies and dance. It&#39;s completely concert.
In this AWS Summit Tokyo 2019, 33,000+ have been registered. AWS has 50% share in cloud business, it&#39;s great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-05-31: AWS DeepRacer League Workshop</title>
      <link>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:10:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naomori.github.io/journal/posts/2019-05-31/</guid>
      <description>AWS DeepRace League - Technical Workdshop Yesterday, I joined the &amp;ldquo;AWS Deep Racer League - Technical Workhop&amp;rdquo;, because I wanted to have fun learning about machine learning. The AWS DeepRacer is a 1/18 scale racing car and it makes it possible to learn Reinforcement Learning (RL) in a fun way. It was disappointing that the hands-on was disabled due to a failure of the AWS service.
The presenter explained DeepRacer&#39;s Reinforcement Learning and its simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>